review	label
He can use the bubbles floating to the sodas top to prove the air is trying to escape.	0
He might uses the evidence that gas bubbles in soda float to the top so the gas particles will go to the top of the box too.	3
That gas goes up.	0
Sam will try to prove his claim by experimenting and doing research with soda.	0
the gas bubble in soda float to the top so the gas bubbles in a box could float to the top as well. also when you blow up a balloon the gas particles could go to the edges of the balloon to make it expand outward	3
beacaues gas goes up cause it has air	0
I think that Sam will use the point of bubbles floating to the top in a soda to support his diagram.	0
will she is smart	0
"Yes, the gas bubble in the soda float to the top."	0
"Sam could use this in his evidence by saying that particles always rise to the top,like a soda can."	3
The soda bubbles went to the top.	0
Because of the soda	0
"Sam can use the evidence of the balloon as well because as a balloon grows bigger when you blow it, the particles go up, which causes it to grow up and bigger."	0
Sam can use the evidence that gas bubbles float up to the top of the soda when it's open.	0
The particles will act like the soda.	0
Sam might use the evidence to support his saying that the gas particles in soda float to the very top. He might use it in a paragraph or essay.	0
because his teacher said that gas bubbles in soda float to the top	0
"I think Sam will use this evidence like this, Gas bubbles in soda float to the top. This proves that gas particles go together and rise to the top of any container they are in."	3
it can save his claim by making it right	0
he could say the teacher was his source	0
that maybe he will think that the particles will make the sugar go down.	0
sam used a lot of evidende and he is explainning how it affects it.	0
sam might use this evidence to support his claim because the gas bubbles float to the top	0
Sam may be able to use the evidence that gas bubbles in soda float to top and say that my claim is correct because in my drawing all the particles are on the top.	3
"Since in soda gas particles go up, so can the gas particles in the box."	3
Sam is not correct because they would not go to the top.	0
he will say that since there gas bubbles they floated to the top	0
"For example, when you shake a bottle of soda, gas bubbles in the soda float to the top."	0
"Sam could say that gas bubbles in soda will rise because it is less dense than the material surrounding it, which is soda. This supports Sam's claim that gas bubbles will rise to the top after 1 minute because the gas particle might be less dense than it's surrounding environment, and therefore will rise to the top."	3
Sam can use the soda evidence because it supports his claim of gas rising upwards to the ceiling.	0
"""Gas bubbles in soda float to the top"". This is perfect to use as evidence to back up Sam's drawing claim thing. It's exactly what they're talking about."	3
Sam is right because Charlies is correct already.	0
Sam might use any of his evidence to support his claim because the with soda the fizz will push the particles out like if it wants to explode.	0
the gas cauases a reaction for the bubbles to go up.	0
Sam would use the gas bubbles evidence to show that the particles are not spaced out.	0
Sam might use the evidence that gas bubbles in soda float to the top.	0
"Sam would use the bubbles float to the top by saying that all gas particles are like gas bubbles, and go to the top."	0
"Gas particles can float the air up the sky because when you put baking soda and vinegar, it fizzle to make gas."	0
the particles rise like gas bubbles.	0
"Gas bubble in soda will definitely float to the top if it was contained of gas. Sam might say that, the gas in the bubbles help them float upwards the top. When one minute passes, the gas particles will soon float to the top. This is because the gas is causing movement."	3
Because of the carbonation in the soda that forms gas bubbles to rise to the top.	0
Sam might use the evidence to show how all the particles are moving together at the top.	0
gas from soda raises to the top just like how they are in this box	3
she might thiink that the particals are the bubbles that flot to the top	0
sam bubble are on the top	0
Sam might use this evidence to support his claim by saying gas bubbles in soda float to the top just like these gas bubbles.	3
He might say that this type of gas is found in soda.	0
gas particles will go to the top of the box because in a soda bottle the gas bubbles float to the top .	3
Sam might use this information because the particles got bigger and floated.	0
Sam will use the evidence that gas bubbles float to the top in soda as this almost mirrors his explanation of how particles float to the top of a container. He will relate the gas bubbles to the gas particles by saying that they both act in a similar way as they are both gases.	3
The sugar particles float to the top because the water was evaporating and the sugar moved up	0
because when you blow air they are not gas bubbles in your air i dont think.But in the soda the gas bubbles rise.	0
Because the gas bubbles will float on the top when you shake a soda can.	0
"Sam might use this evidence to support his claim that the particles are all at the top because the gas bubbles in soda will float to the top, and the gas bubbles are basically gas particles so it will go to the top too."	3
"Because she drew that the gas particles rise all the way to the top, just like the teacher explained."	0
she could use this evidence by say that the gas rises	0
Sam might use this evidence to support his claim because his illustration matches the description of gas bubbles floating to the top of the soda can.	3
"Sam can use his evidence to support his claim by saying after one minute the gas particles goes to the top, just like when gas bubbles in soda go to the top."	3
it can support his claim because it relates to his answer	0
"He could maybe use it to explain how when you open up soda the gas particles rise to the top. Therefore, maybe after one minute the gas particles will rise to the top when the box is opened."	3
When you shake a soda all of its gas particles rise up to the lid so its the same for the gas particles in the box.	3
Sam could use this example of soda gas bubbles to support his claim by making a comparison on what where the air bubbles go and what the gas particles do in a minute.	0
He could use gas bubbles float to the top in soda	0
because he can use the evidence to support his claim	0
Sam might use the evidence stated above by his teacher. The teacher also didn't say that he was wrong.	0
because it's important.	0
the bolle foot to the top	0
He might say that if the gas bubble go to the top so do the gas particles	0
he might use it to support his claim	0
Gas bubbles in soda float to the top so bubbles in gas float in the top too.	3
he could say that in his drawings he was drawing soda bubbles that are floating to the top	0
Sam can use this evidence that the teacher gave him because it includes how the gas makes the bubbles go to the top.	0
The soda has gas bubbles that rise to the top when they are being left in a bottle.	0
He might use the evidence that hot air balloon particle goes up because there is a high temp inside the balloon	0
"Now, Sam knows that in soda, gas particles also rise to the top, so he knows that his claim is correct because he has this evidence."	3
still confused?	0
because the air particles evaporate.	0
I think that Sam might use the evidence that gas bubbles in soda float to the top to support his claim.	0
that when particles have less mass they go up.	0
"Both the information shown can help support Charlie's claim is because his claim shows that hi gas particles are going up top, and how some of his gas particles are going in different directions so that can help support his claim by both evidence."	0
Sam might use this evidence to support his claim because he needs evidence to support his claim.	0
Sam might use this evidence to support his claim to show that the drawing of particles can be used as evidence of the fact that gas bubbles in soda move to the top.	0
He can use his evidence to prove what particles will do in a soda bottle.	0
Sam can use this to support his evidence because when the soda bubbles float up to the top the gas particles can do that to like the bubbles in a soda can.	3
"His evidence showed that because gas is lighter than a liquid, the gas will reach the top over an elapsed period of time."	0
"Since the gas bubbles go up, that means that the particles should move up too. But the only problem here is that gas bubbles in soda go up right away, but they are talking about one minute later. But y that time, the gas particles in soda mostly disappear."	3
Gas particles get to the top because they are lighter than the other particles in a soda bottle	3
Sam can use that evidence cause it still supports his claim.	0
because he put them all at the top.	0
"Sam could use this to support his claim by saying that the gas bubbles in the soda are going to the top, so his diagram is correct."	3
He can imagine that the box is a soda can and the dots are the gas bubbles which come up when you open the soda can. So he can say that the gas particles move up .	3
I think that sam might use this evidence because in some air or gas particles flow up to float in the air.	0
"Sam might say that "" My claim is correct because, based on the data, my teacher said, ""Gas bubbles in soda float to the top"". This is similar to what I drew."""	3
I think Sam is saying that the little particles float up because the air takes it up since the air evaporates to the clouds.	0
Sam would say that the gas bubbles rise to the top of soda so the gas will always rise not spread out.	3
"Sam might use the ""Gas bubbles in soda float to the top."" evidence because his picture shows particles rising up after a minute, proving that his picture is correct. I don't think he'll use the other evidence to support his claim because it doesn't show what Sam's picture shows."	3
"Sam's claim is that the particles are all grouped together at the top of the box. The evidence that gas bubbles in soda float to the top is similar to what Sam thinks is happening to the gas particles in the box. This evidence shows that since the gas bubbles in soda rise up to the top, the gas particles in the box may do the same."	3
"Sam might say that the evidence supports his claim because if the gas bubbles float to the top, the particles will also. His model shows that the particles are at the top."	3
"I think Sam might use this evidence to support his claim by saying, he gas bubbles are at the top in a soda like in his diagram on the gas particles in a box, using the evidence,""Gas bubbles in a soda float to the top."""	3
"Since his claim is that particles will stay on the top, he can use the evidence ""Gas bubbles stay on top"" because that situation proves that his statement is correct. In his picture, it shows that all the particles move from the bottom to the top. In soda's that gas particles that fizz are always on the top."	0
Sam might use this evidence by saying that gas particles all float up in soda so they must do the same thing in air.	3
Sam might use any of this evidence to support his claim that the particles are all at the top because in the soda scenario all the gas bubbles in the soda floated to the top.	3
That the the box is enlarging.	0
"I think Sam can use this evidence because he drew the gas particles at the top already, but he could use the balloon evidence too. He might think that after a while the gas particles float to the top of the balloon."	0
because soda particles flow up to the top maybe these particles will too	3
sam will use the bottle evidence to support his claim because his model is closest to the bottle evidence and sam will say that if the box was a bottle and the molecules were air bubbles the bubbles would go up to the top of the box	3
In his picture all the gas particles went up	0
He will use the evidence that the teacher said.	0
the gas particles in the soda would rise to the top. would support the claim that gas particles in the box would rise to the top.	3
He could use the evidence to say that the bubbles float to the top so the particles are on the top.	0
I think Sam will use it to support his claim and to prove wrong the other answers.	0
"The gas particles go to the top, like in soda"	3
Sam might use any of this evidence to support his claim because if gas bubbles rise so do particles.	0
It might support his claim because his diagram might be about how the gas particles inside a soda move and how they rise.	3
The gas particles inside the bubble rise to the top of the container because gas bubbles in soda float to the top.	3
cause he had all the particales to the top and then they had moved little by litte.	0
I think Sam might think gas bubbles in soda float to the top and the box and soda both have gas particles in them so they will both float to the top.	3
"He might use the evidence that 'Gas bubble float to the top', and it means that everything would go up at the same time."	0
"Sam might use this evidence to support his claim because gas bubbles in soda float to the top, just like his particles did."	3
Sam might use this information as evidece in his argument.	0
Sam might the gas bubbles in soda float to the top evidence to support his claim that the particles are all at the top.	3
"When gas bubbles in soda float to the top, Sam can use this evidence to support his claim by saying that if gas bubbles in soda can float to the very top, then gas particles can too because they are practically the same the thing."	3
Sam might use this evidence to support his claim because gas particles in a soda float to the top just like they did in his notebook.	3
He might use the soda statement to say my particles will rise too.	0
Sam might use this to support his claim by saying that the soda particles floated on the top.	0
He might say that the particle are the gas bubbles in a soda cup.	0
Sam might use the fact that gas bubbles in soda float to the top.	0
"Sam can use any of this evidence to support his claim because his claim was that gas particles are all at the top, and some particles in an air balloon also go to the top."	2
He can observe the gas particles in a soda.	0
The first piece of evidence	0
"Sam might use the evidence that gas bubbles in soda float to the top because in his drawing, it shows all the particles at the top."	3
"Sam might use this as his evidence to support his claim because he argues that the gas particles will float to the top. Well, that is the same thing happening in the soda bottle with the bubbles since the bubbles is air."	3
"Sam might use any evidence by saying that because when you blow air into a balloon, the air goes everywhere, it could all go the the top, and in soda, gas particles go up."	3
because it bubbles in a soda so it went to the top	0
because the teacher said that the soda particles floated to the top	0
