review	label
Sam might have this information as evidence because the teacher used he word gas and she explained that it goes up to the top.	0
He could tell them how gas floats up and how it tries to get out of the room from the roof.	0
Sam can use the soda one saying that If in soda gas floats to the top creating bubbles why would my box not do the same?	3
"Sam could say that they might rise to the top like gas bubbles, but no air is entering the box so the balloon statement won't help."	0
"Sam might say that not all of the bubbles in soda go to the top because the rest of the drink is still super bubbly. In a balloon, the particles spread out and blow up the balloon in every direction."	0
"Sam might use the evidence of soda bubbles to support his claim, because they float to the top, just like his particles in the box."	3
"I think that Sam might use any of this evidence to support his claim because he could argue that a balloon only expands outward because of the force of the person blowing into it. However, the bubbles in a soda go up on their own."	0
"Sam could use the soda data because it just shows what gas particles do already, rise to the top. The ballon evidence because balloons try to stay up as long as they can, if gas particles rise, that may be why the fall so slowly."	0
In soda they float all the way to the top from the bottom making him correct because that is what his drawing showcased.	3
When you blow into a ballon it being cramped into a space that it needs to stretch out to fit but our experiment is using a box	0
"If Sam takes a bottle of soda he could show that the gas particles are at the top. He could say that his drawing is like a bottle of soda, so it would look the same."	0
He uses it by saying gas bubbles go up so the gas particles will go up.	0
He could use the one about soda.	0
Sam might say that gas bubbles float to the top and that you need to blow into the balloon for it to expand.	0
"Like I said in the last question, the particles being the gas, floating to the top would be exactly Sam's argument."	0
"he could use it too explain that there kind of the same thing; they both float to the top, and there both gas."	0
Sam could use this evidence to prove his claim because he can say that the gas is in a box so it would make seance that the gas would flout to the top of the box. Just like a soda's gas would in a soda bottle.	3
He might use Gas bubbles in soda float to the top and the one he drew is on top.	3
Sam would use the first piece of evidence to explain why he drew the gas particles on the top.	0
"because the gas takes the bubbles to the top, and the gas is going to the top."	0
it might go like soda	0
"Charlie explains the balloon as a case, but if you insert helium gas into the balloon the balloon will be floating in the air.That is like air going up.
Then particles should float above in space.Like a gas bubbles in soda."	3
By giving an example of something related to this with gas.	0
Yes he can because of the subtance.	0
use soda for an example but don't drink it soda is gross and bad for your teeth	0
The gas in the bubbles is moving up and not spreading around so this means that the gas in the box should go up and not spread out like Charlies claim.	3
to escape	0
"Since Gas bubbles float at the top in soda, they should do that everywhere. Meaning that after a minute the Gas bubbles will just rise."	3
they go to the top because there trying to come out just like a soda the particles inside want to come out that's why when you open a soda the bubbles jump around(out).	3
he could say his bubbles are floating up like in a soda.	3
"He could say that since gas particles in soda float to the top, the gas particles in a box will also move to the top."	3
That his is better than Charlie's evidence.	0
that since the gas gets bigger it goes to the top instead of the middle	0
Sam could use this evidence to support his claim that particles are all on the top because it proves that gas bubbles in soda float to the top	3
he can use the "gas bubbles in soda float to the top" claim.	0
The evidence he can use is the soda one.	0
He might use this example as evidence to support his claim that the particles are all at the top. It supports his reasoning very well. With the evidence stating that gas bubbles float to the top.	0
Show how the gas bubbles in soda float to the top.	0
balloons only blow out like that because of the shape. for example the ones used to make balloon dogs aren't blown out fully meaning the air particles go out to the top just like how they do in soda	0
"Sam could use this evidence by comparing gas molecules to gas bubbles in soda, and how they float to the top."	3
Sam might use the evidence provided to support the claim by stating that the air is denser than the gas particles so the gas particles would float up.	0
Sam will us the evidence that gas bubbles in soda flow to the top to support his claim by stating that is gas bubbles in soda rise then air in a box will rise as well.	3
"Sam could use this information to support his claim by saying that the gas particles in the soda float to the top and the gas particles in the balloon also stretch upwards, which is why the balloon expands."	0
He can say that since gas bubbles in soda it is probably the same in regular air as well.	0
"Sam could use both evidence that his claim is correct because in soda gas particles float to the top and in the balloon, the gas particles also go up when being blown into."	0
Sam will use the evidence of gas bubble floating top the top and use soda as examples.	0
Because the particles go at the edge of the balloon.	0
He can back up his claim by giving it evidence by writing gas bubbles in soda float to the top.	0
Sam will use the evidence that the gas bubbles float to the top to help explain that all of the gas particles are at the top	0
he can use the soda to help hi win the argument	0
When you open up a soda and you hear the snap crackle pop is when they escaped. they first get traped in there and when some one wants to drink that drink the will open it and then the snap crackle pop is the gas particles escaped in the air.	0
because her drwaing shows that the partilces are up just the teacher said the particles of the soda go upp	3
The gas in soda because the gas all rises to the top(but that is pressure).	0
He could explain how whenever you open a soda bottle the gas is always going to separate from the mixture by going up and escaping into the air.	0
"If the box is filled with a liquid, then Sam would be correct because in soda gas bubbles float to the top."	0
"he could says that the the gas is float to the top because the oxygen of the soda and the air needs to be equal so, it float to the top."	0
With the evidence that Sam used with sight that he could see that the gas bubbles are only going straight up like when you shake that soda all the gas bubbles set themselves on the top of the drink.	0
there not at the top	0
Sam may use the first piece of evidence to prove that particles float to the top since the bubbles in soda float to the top.	3
The particles all go to the top but in some cases there are to many and they get pushed down	0
He might recite what the teacher said.	0
Sam might compare how similar his claim to the evidence that gas bubbles in soda float to the top.	0
I think he will use an anolgy.	0
Gas floating to the top.	0
He can use this piece of evidence because if he see's all the bubbles in the soda float o top then he will or might be right	0
Sam might use the evidence "Gas bubbles float to the top" as an example to support his claim and to prove that Charlie's contrasting claim is incorrect due to this fact.	0
in a room thre particles stay near the ceiling and dont escape cause its a closed enclosure.	0
"Yes, because the particle will settle up."	0
He used that because it like that what he think.	0
"As stated, the gas particles rise in the soda, therefore, gas should rise up like it does in the soda."	3
Sam will use this evidence to prove that gas particles float up.	0
He might explain how gas bubbles in soda floats to the top just like how gas float to the top after one minute in a box.	3
If gas bubbles in a soda float to the top it is also like how the gas bubbles in the box float to the top to try and escape the box and how the bubbles in the soda are trying to escape the can.	3
"When you blow into a balloon, you are pushing the air to the side. With soda there is no human interaction."	0
Sam thinks like the soda is the air and the soda gas is gas. That all the air will separate with the gas.	0
the balloon will float cause the gas is moving up	0
"Sam might use the bubble example to support his claim that the pritcles would rise as a form of evidence that particles, in this case the air in the bubbles, float to the top of their given space, in that case the bottle."	0
Because air is a gas and even going in all the directions its still going up	0
The bubbles are all at the top due to all the gas particles and liquid substances at the top.	0
"In charlies drawing, it shows all the particles are on the top, which doesn't support that the particles bounce in all directions."	0
Sam is a man so he is always right. No evidence needed	0
"Sam can say that because gas bubbles in a soda float to the top, gas particles in the box also floats to the top."	3
"As the can was opened, the gas particles floated to the top."	0
Sam might use any of the evidence because the gas can move apart and out at the same time.	0
He used the soda example	0
Becauseof the gas	0
He might use the evidence that gas bubbles in soda float to the top to support his claim.	0
He can support his claim with his evidence because it proves his point.	0
That the particles are supposed to rise to the top.	0
"The gas bubbles in the soda are at the top of the bottle, in a closed space. He can use this to support his claim because the box is also a closed space, same with the soda bottle or can."	0
Sam will use this evidence to tell how they react like that and relate it.	0
"Sam will say that because gas floats to the top in soda, gas should also float to the top when inside of a box."	3
Gas bubbles in soda float to the top just like how the particles in this one did.	3
He might state a comparison to the gas particles and the soda bubbles and how they both rise the top.	3
the particals move because of what makes it move	0
he can say if you shake a soda the gas bubbles will go to the to	0
i think he did something wrong	0
I think he might use the same information I typed in the last page.	0
She can use this evidence to support her claim because in her drawing it says the the gas particle rises up. One piece of evidence that she can use is that the gas bubbles in soda float to the top.	3
He might say that the gas bubbles carry the particles up with them.	0
"since they all started at the bottom, they will all end up at the top"	0
He might use it because it talks about how the gas floats up.	0
Sam might use this information because it will support his claim.	0
"well, only the evidence given to him works"	0
he might state that if the soda gas particles can float to the top why would these be any diffrent then the soda particles.	0
"Sam can use the evidence on how gas bubbles in soda float to the top, but in addition he can also say that in a balloon air particle go to the top also which is supporting his claim."	0
"He might say that because gas bubbles float to the top in a can , gas particles will do the same thing."	3
He would use the first piece of evidence to show how bubbles float to the top soda	0
"Sam might use any of this evidence to support his claim that the particles are all at the top because the gas bubbles in soda float to the top and because if a balloon grows bigger in all different places, it floats to the top too."	3
'- he can use the evidence to support his claim that the particles are all at the top because it says -GAS BUBBLES in soda FLOAT TO THE TOP-	3
"Sam could say that gas bubbles in soda float to the top and when you blow air into a balloon, since it is going all directions, that means it is also going to the top."	0
sam think that like gas bubbles suger will go up	0
Sam might use the soda bubbles for his claim.	0
He might have made a model to show how the gas bubbles float up in soda to support his claim.	0
Sam might have used the evidence that the teacher gave to support the claim that the gas particles rise to the top like a soda so he thought about a soda and how the particles would rise to the top.	3
"Sam could use this evidence to support this claim by, explaining that the gas bubbles in soda float to the top, so why shouldn't the particles in the box."	3
Because all the bubbles are at the top. LIke how the gas in the soda is at the top.	0
the gas can change shape and move around	0
Because in his drawing the bubbles rise to the top just like soda	3
they can float to the top	0
If soda particles float to the top these might too.	3
"Because all his particles are at the top, instead spread out."	0
"he could tell everyone that the gas particles float to the sides, like in the soda"	0
gas bubbles float to the top	0
He might say that the particals are giong to rise to the surface.	0
Sam is saying that all the gas bubbles are going to rise to the top like the bubbles in soda do.	3
that when you open a soda gas goes on top	0
"The bubbles rise to the top to find air and not be stuck trying to bounce around in liquid, so they rise up to find air."	0
That the gas bubbles in soda rise to the top so his bubbles rise to the top.	3
"Sam could use this as evidence to support his claim, because when you blow up a balloon, the gas particles float to the top, but then they fill up the top and fills in all the other gaps."	0
"In soda, the gas floats to the top of the soda. This means that gas floats up."	3
When you shake soda it goes upwards instead of going everywhere like it wants to get out.	0
The gas bubbles will float to the top creating fizz aka bubbles	0
that gas goes up and out.	0
He can take a fast motion video to prove that the bubble float to the top	0
He may use this evidence to show that all the gas particles rise to the top	0
"Sam might use the proof that the bubbles float to the top in soda to back up his claim. He could claim that because the bubbles in soda rise to the top, all gas particles will rise to the top."	3
He would use the first piece of evidence and take it as an example/model of what would happen in his box.	0
It is an example of how his claim is true.	0
"Sam could use both pieces of evidence to support his claim. The gas bubbles in a soda float to the top which is what he claimed. Balloons, when filled with a certain type of air, remain in the air instead of following the laws of gravity. This is the gas particles wanting to float to the top but they can't because they are trapped."	3
Sam will use this evidence by saying that this evidence is an example of his claim. His drawing shows the particles going to the top and this evidence shows just that.	0
"Sam believes that the particles would drift to the top, and since the gas particles in the soda flow to the top as well, this supports his claim. To then, further is claim he could use the soda scenario to show how the gas particle drift to the top in everyday scenarios."	3
"Gas particles like the ones in the box are also found in soda. Just like in soda, the gas particles would rise to the top of the container."	3
Sam would use the soda experiment/observation as an example that his claim is correct.	0
Sam might use this evidence to support his claim of the gas particles going all the way up. The evidence is when the teacher said that gas bubbles float all the way up in sodas.	3
I think that Sam will use the argument of gas bubbles in soda floating to the top of soda because it is similar to his claim that the gas particles will rise to the top of the box. Sam will use this to support the claim he made because it closely relates to the situation that he is working with.	3
"he might say that gas particles always go to the top and he might use the soda as an example to prove his point because the particles are the same, the only thing that has changed is the fact that there is water in the equation now"	3
he will say that similar to how gas bubbles move up in soda the gas bubbles will move up in the box.	3
"Sam could say ""Gas always rises to the top because of gravity, and that is why balloons go up."""	0
"That gas particles float to the top in a soda can, so they do in a box too."	3
He might say that since bubbles in soda float to the top that means the gas is going up.	0
if the gas bubbles in soda go to the top then so should the gas particles in the box	3
"In Soda the gas bubbles all float to the top, so the gas molecules probably do the same when they are not in soda"	3
Gas bubbles in soda float to the top. That means gas particles float to the top.	3
"He might use this to compare the two to eachother, even though they are not completly the same sitution."	0
That the gas bubbles in soda floats straight to the top	0
He will use this to support his claim because gas particles are like gas bubbles and how they both float to the top means that the gas particles must float to the top.	0
"Sam could say that when you just leave soda alone, like they left the box, the gas bubbles rise to the top by themselves. He could then say that when blowing air into a balloon, the gas particles are being assisted, and might only spread out everywhere because of the breath that you are blowing in."	0
The gas in a soda will float up just like the gas in a balloon will float up to make the balloon float.	0
He might use the evidence that soda particles float to the top.	0
He can use the evidence to support his claim. It helps him to have proof.	0
this evidence supports sam in this scenario because air wants to escape so it floats to the top.	0
Sam might use the evidence about the gas rising to the top in soda because his claim is about how gas will rise to the top.	3
Sam will use the gas bubbles because they prove his hypothesis is correct.	0
Sam might use this to try to tell the similarities between them and explain that he is right.	0
Sam would use the evidence to relate to his drawing as in both situations(the box and the soda) the gas is reacting the same.	0
Sam knows that gas bubbles in soda float to the top.	0
He might make some type of experiment that can represent the process of a soda when it is opened.	0
"Sam might use the evidence ""Gas bubbles in soda float to the top,"" because his diagram shows that gas will float to the top."	3
Sam can use the first peice of information to support him because he thinks that the gas particles will rise.	0
He will use it in the way that soda bubbles float to the top.	0
Sam would show that Gas bubbles in soda rise to the top.	0
Sam might say that the reason the air goes in every direction in a balloon is because that your breath is the reason why the gas particles move like that.	0
"Gas particles in soda float to the top, but not all of them."	0
"Sam would most likely support his claim with the example of a soda can. If the bubbles rise to the top in a soda can, then why wouldn't they rise to the top in a box?"	3
Sam could say that since gas bubble float to the top in soda they float to the top anywhere.	3
Sam will use his teachers evidence about gas particles in soda going to the top	0
Sam might use the evidence that gas bubbles in soda float to the top because it agrees with his claim.	3
"Sam could use this information to his advantage by comparing the box to the can of soda, and claiming that they will both rise."	0
The gas can't change the shape of the container	0
"Sam could say that the particles are floating at the top, because they become lighter and lighter as they dissolve."	0
He can use these pieces to help him because that means that particles do go to the top.	0
Sam may use molecules to the top as evidence due to his drawing being spread out.	0
"When soda had gas bubbles, they go straight upwards, like the gas bubbles in Sam's drawing."	0
"Sams bubbles went up to the top like it does with soda, he represents this in his drawing."	3
Sam believes that all as particles will rise to the top. The gas bubbles in soda float to the top and this strongly supports Sam's claim.	3
Sam will say that gas bubbles in soda rise and the air you blow into a balloon isn't gas.	0
"Sam could argue what he originally did with the idea that gas bubbles float to the top. He could also argue that in the case of the balloon, that the particles would go to the top, but the material of the balloon would make it expand in all directions."	0
"I think Sam will say that when gas bubbles enter a soda the bubbles will float to the top of the soda. He will say that because of the evidence that his teacher provided him with and if it was an argument say something like, ""I don't think your claim works Charlie, because the balloon is a different unique shape."	3
"Sam could use the first piece of evidence. In his drawing, all the gas particles are at the top. This is similar to when you open a soda; all the gas bubbles head to the top and sometimes overflow."	3
Because they used a bolloon.	0
Pressure explains where they all go.	0
He will use this evidence by showing something that he knows to be true to help him strengthen his claim.	0
In soda the bubbles flout to the top.	0
sam would use the evidence to help him prove his point by saying the carbon in the soda is pushing all of the gas trapped in it to the top.	0
so that he is right	0
"Sam would use this evidence because if the gas bubbles float to the top, then gas bubbles must ALWAYS do that."	3
he will say that in a soda all the bubbles go to the top.	0
he might put soda in a see through cup and show people for evidence	0
the bubbles rise	0
Sam could use the fact that gas bubbles float to the top of the soda can and say that that would happen in the box aswell.	3
Gas bubbles in soda float to the top.	0
"Gas bubbles in soda float to the top. This means that when the gas particles are in the box, the particles eventually all float to the top."	3
"Sam could say that because the gas floats to the top of soda, the air will rise to the top."	3
That the particle are like gas bubbles.	0
"When you put helium in a balloon, The balloon will start going up. And helium is a gas."	0
"He might say that since the gas bubbles are on bottom, gradually they'll float up just like in a soda."	3
"When the as bubbles on the top, the gas bubbles are beginning to move on the top."	0
The bubbles in a soda rushes out to the area it was opened by.	0
"Using the gas bubbles evidence, Sam's claim is particles floating up, like the evidence."	0
"Since gas bubbles in soda float to the top, then gas particles in a box would float to the top as well."	3
when you shake a bottle all the particles go on top and just stay there till the movement has no more movement.	0
He would tell us when the box runs out of air the gas particals floats to the top.	0
The gas particles float to the top because its trying to grow the box.	0
this evidence is the claim of that they go up when you open or do something	0
SAM might use any of this evidence to support his claim that the particles are all in the top by using the teachers claim and use that of any of his evidence.	0
Sam will use a bunch of sodas and open them and when he does he will hear a noise and that will be the particles getting out of the bottle	0
"Sam could say that the soda bubbles float to the top of the bottle, thus the gas particles would do the same."	3
"That since Gas bubbles can float to the top of a soda can, then so can particles in a box. Also, if particles in a box were to float around, then the box would get bigger, or float."	3
He will use the Soda evidence to explain how the gas particles float to the top.	0
"Sam would say that particles would float since in soda, the gas particles float to the top just like in his diagram."	3
He might use the balloon evidence by saying the air goes around the sides of the balloon.	0
I think that Sam will use this evidence to support his claim because in his picture it shows that the bubbles have moved all the way to the top and that the bubbles in a soda move all the way to the top	3
Blow the balloon would be evidence but not really gas bubbles in a soda/POP.	0
"Gas particles like to jump in every direction, so when the bubbles want to float to the top, the gas particles are jumping around."	0
if the gas on the soda go up so the gas on the box will go up too	3
by bribing the teacher	0
"the aif would fly over the plece, but they finilly go to thd top."	0
with pressure the gas in soda go up to the top	0
Same would think that if the gas bubbles in the soda do float up then the particles in this container should float up.	0
The particles in a soda must act the same way the particles in a box does.	0
because they are going to the top and staying	0
because that is what he thinks	0
Because it is an example on the picture he drew	0
the heat is going down by slow	0
the gas bubbles would go to the top because the gas in the soda is always floating at the top.	0
because all of the bubbles	0
"Because if the particles in the box act like they would in a soda, then the particles will all go up."	3
this was a gorilla type of survey sponsored by gorilla glue and gorilla tape	0
"soda's gas bubbles fly to the top,in sam's notebook,that's what the drawing looks like"	3
"Sam would most likely use the evidence of that gas bubbles from soda float to the top as a way to support his claim that the particles float to the top, just like soda."	3
Sam can use this as his evidence because those types of particles are all clumped up together.	0
The fizzing after opening up a soda can is the gas particles meaning it has to be at the top if its gonna be fizzing that loud and you can hear it pretty well so it has to be at the top and if it were to be at the bottom or anywhere else you wouldn't hear it as well as you could it hear when the gas particles are at the top.	0
He could use this as his claim because gas from soda rise to the top so all gas should rise to the top	3
"The gas bubbles are in soda and the carbonation makes the bubbles float to the top and his picture in his notebook shows everything to explain, nut maybe he should label it to make it easier for people to understand."	0
"Sam could use the evidence that gas bubbles float to the top in soda to support his claim. It supports it because if he states that gas goes up, gas going up in a soda can would be an example of gas particles going up, which helps his claim."	3
"Sam might say that since bubbles are light, the gravity only affects them a little bit, not much."	0
He would say that the particles move in different directions to make it round then some particles would push the balloon up to make the tip of it.	0
"The gas particles become spaced out when your blowing into a balloon, but we are not blowing air into a box ."	0
I think that he can use that the air of the soda is at the top is because it was the calcium out of the drink	0
"Sam might use this evidence to support his claim that the particles are all at the top because when gas bubbles appear in soda they rise to the top, and when you blow air into a balloon, part of the gas particles go to the top."	3
He might use that Gas bubbles in soda float to the top. Only because that is what the claim states.	3
Sam's evidence supports his claim because once you open a can of soda the bubbles then float to the top.	0
Sam can say the acidity in soda quickly goes up as the soda is poured out.	0
He will say they are all on top but many directions at the top	0
Sam may use this as evidence in order to support his claim because the gas rise in soda and should not be different if this was to take place elsewhere.	3
Sam may use the soda as his evidence because if the gases rose to the top then how would it expand the can.	0
You can see the gas bubbles appearing to the top of the soda when you first open the can.	0
"Sam might use this evidence to show that the particles moved fast upwards because the pressure being released to the gas bubbles are fast and hot, causing lots of energy in the particles, moving them up."	0
sam might use his evidence that supports his drawing of the box because he would say that the box of gas particles is like a soda bottle all of the gas particles float to the top and don't stay on the bottom.	3
"If the particles are able to go all different directions in the balloon, then it should be able to go to the top of the soda because the particle have no other place to go."	0
Sam could say that the gas particles will float to the top because gas bubbles in soda float to the top.	3
"I think Sam might use this evidence to support his claim that the particles are all at the top because he knows that if the gas bubbles in soda float to the top, then his claim would probably be right."	3
"Sam might write something like, "" when gas is on one end, and doesn't really have anywhere to go, it tends to move upward."""	0
Gas always floats to the top if air there is any empty air space. That's why when soda bubbles float to the top of the bottle it's because there is air space at the top.	3
"She can claim that the balloon grows bigger because the gas is rising to the top of the balloon, stretching it out to make it bigger."	0
"Since he drawing of the gas going to the top he can relate it to soda, once you open up a soda it right away floats to the top."	3
Sam could use the evidence about the soda because the soda gas particles are floating on top and Sam's claim is that gas particles float on top. So the evidence can back up his claim.	0
Sam might use this evidence by saying that the bubbles just like the particles rise to the top. Also the balloon starts growing bigger from the top since all the particles hit the top of the balloon.	3
the air spreads	0
"his evidence is the soda bubbles, they rise up to the top"	0
He thinks that sense the gas in the can goes all the way to the top the gas particles are going to go to the top too.	3
He might use this evidence and might get it right but like its not in a soda can but a balloon it grows and that could be the right answer.	0
because it shows it	0
He could use the bubble example since they both rise up fast and the gas and bubbles clump up at the top	0
Sam might use the evidence to support his claim by putting a helium filled balloon inside a box	0
"When you blow into a balloon, the balloon isn't a perfect round shape, it is bigger at the top of the balloon. When gas is trapped and can be released, it will try to find a way to be released."	0
the gas in sodas float to the top therefore the gas particles are up at the top of the page	3
Sam will say that balloons are growing bigger in all direction because they are blowing gases into the balloon. He will also use the information about soda to support his statement.	0
"When a balloon is blown the air is trapped inside,but, when more air is blown inside the original air that was inside can get pushed up to the top."	0
Sam might use this evidence to support his claim that the particles are all at the top because gas bubbles float to the top of a soda can once it is opened and this supports his claim in is diagram for the gas particles all floating to the top.	3
I think Sam will use the evidence "Gas bubbles in soda float to the top." because it is the same evidence on what Sam did.	3
Gas bubbles in soda float to the top.	0
"Gas bubbles in soda float to the top, so in this case with the box, the same thing will happen."	3
Sam could use the evidence which states that gas bubbles in soda float to the top as his drawing represented gas bubbles moving to the top of an area after a minute.	3
Sam could use the example about soda because the gas in the soda floated to the top. Just like how Sam's gas particles rose to the top of the area.	3
"Sam could use both of the pieces of information because as I said before, the gas particles in soda float to the top like Sam's drawing. The balloon information could support his claim by showing that the air is trying to float to the top but doesn't know where up is so goes in all directions."	3
"Sam can use the evidence to prove his claim by stating the air that is in the box alongside the particles, and the air can be denser than the gas particles, so therefore, the gas particles would float up."	0
Sam's drawing is similar to a soda bottle or can where the bubbles float to the top. He could also argue that the air in a balloon is pushing on the outside edges of the balloon to make it grow bigger.	3
"Sam could state; In glasses of soda, bubbles , air particles , rise to the top. Therefore, if you replace the glass with the box the particles should float to the top again. Also, if you blown air into a balloon the gas particles could float to the edges of the balloon and push outward causing it to expand."	3
Sam may have used have used this evidence to support this claim because gas in a can moves to the top so therefore gas in this space must move to the top.	3
Sam can use the evidence about gas bubbles floating to the top of the soda to support his claim. This evidence can help him because it supports why particles should float to the top (move to the top) of any container.	3
He could use the evidence and say that since gas in soda goes up the gas in the container would also go up	3
"Sam might use any of this evidence to support his claim that the particles are all at the top by, using the evidence that gas bubbles in soda float to the top. His claim and the evidence both state that gas bubbles go to the top."	3
Sam might use the statement that "gas bubbles in soda float to the top" to support his claim. This is the only of the two examples that shows how his statement could work. Having this example could also serve to explain why he believes his claim.	0
"Sam could use the evidence about the gas bubbles in soda floating to the top to support his claim because in his drawing, all the gas bubbles are at the top. The evidence about the balloon, however, wouldn't be very helpful to his claim."	3
"When you blow up a balloon you, all the gas particles are packed together, which is why it is expanding. All the gas is trying to go upwards, but there is a lot of gas, so it has no where else to go."	0
"The gas particles in the box rise to the top after a minute, similar to how gas bubbles in soda float to the top. In both examples, the gas particles rise to the top."	3
"""Oh the gas in the balloon just go to the top and make it float! Cause that what soda do."" says Sam. (purposeful use of incorrect grammar)

""No, Just no."" the teacher says
""It would just make thee balloon look like a cloth on a stick."""	0
"The particles in the box will float to the top because in soda, gas bubbles float to the top. This shows that when gas in less dense that what is around it, if will go to the top."	3
The gas bubbles in soda float to the top and the gas particles in the box should too.	3
Sam might use any of this evidence to support his claim that the particles are all at the top by telling about how all the gas rises to the top of the soda	3
"Sam can really only use the fact that gas bubbles in soda float to the top, because if he used the other fact, that would go against his claim, and then he would be agreeing with Charlie. Gas bubbles in sodas float and gather at the top of the bottle like Sam's drawing, so that would be his strongest piece of evidence he could use in his argument."	3
He will use the first set of evidence because like the soda he might be correct by saying that a the gas bubbles float to the top overtime.	3
"I think Sam might use this evidence to support his reasoning because if the soda bubbles rise to the top of the glass in soda because of density, then there is no evidence that there might be another, more dense substance in the box which, because of density, would cause the gas particles to rise to the top of the box."	3
Sam would use the evidence of gas bubbles in soda floating to the top to support his claim of the gas particles going to the top of the box.	3
"Sam could use the first piece of information to say that if gas bubbles float to the top in a soda, then the same thing should happen in the box."	3
Sam caN USE THAT THE PARTICLES ARE EVENY SPACED	0
Sam could use the first piece of information showing how the gas bubbles in soda work similarly to gas particles as they are both gas related.	0
"Sam could use the first piece of evidence about bubbles floating to the top, and relate it to his claim about how gas particles rise to the top."	3
Sam might use the evidence "Gas bubbles in soda float to the top" to show why the particles would move upward.	3
"If there are gas particles in a less dense environment, the gas-particles float to the top."	0
The gas is at the top because in soda gas floats to the top too	3
Sam could use the first piece of information the teacher provided to support his claim. Sam's claim of all the gas molecules at the top of the container is the same as gas bubbles floating on top of soda.	3
Sam would use the evidence of the gas bubbles in soda because they rise up to the top just like in his claim.	3
Sam could use the fact that gas bubbles rise to the top of the soda as evidence to prove that the gas particles are at the top because the gas bubbles are floating to the top in both scenarios.	3
"Sam will probably use the soda evidence to support his claim. That is, that his drawing is similar to the way the soda gas particles are located."	0
"Sam could state the following. Gas particles rise directly upwards. In a bottle of soda, the gas bubbles move directly to the top. These gas particles must rise directly upwards, so the particles in the example must do so as well."	3
The "Gas bubbles in soda float to the top" supports Sam's claim. Sam states that the gas particles go to the other side/top. The quote shows that the gas particles do float to the top.	0
"Sam can say that since gas bubbles float to the top in soda, the gas particles must float to the top as stated in his picture."	3
"Sam might use any of this evidence to support his claim that the particles are all at the top, by proving the similarities of this statement,""Gas bubbles in soda float to the top."""	3
"Since gas bubbles float to the top, Sam's drawing showed molecules at the top"	0
Sam would use this to support his claim because gas bubbles float to the top in soda similar to his prediction and in a balloon the particles spread all different direction including the top.	3
"Sam could argue that all gas particles go up because when there are gas bubbles in soda, they all go to the top. Concluding with his picture being correct."	3
Sam might use the soda evidence because it says gas particles just go upwards.	0
Sam used his logic to come to the conclusion all gas rises.	0
"Sam could us the balloon evidence, because since balloons float, then that must mean the gases are pushing upward and since they push upward, then all the gases are up top."	2
Sam could use the fact that gas bubbles rise to the top as evidence to prove that gas particles rise to the top.	3
"His picture shows thye gas at the top which is what really happens,when you get some soda you see little bubbles that make a sound and they even flout."	0
that the particles are gases bubbles floating to the top	0
"Since the gas bubbles in soda float to the top, the gas particles in the box will too."	3
the gases are trying to push the box open.	0
"Sam might use the soda evidence because his drawing depicts the gas particles as bubbles in the soda, floating to the top."	3
"Sam can use this information by stating how his claim was that gas particles float to the top of their contained space, and in a soda bottle all of the gas particles float up to the top."	0
because they act that way in soda	0
he might use this soda example to say he right because when you open a soda gas comes out of it and it all goes to the top	0
He might say that all gas particles just go up in one shape.	0
"He could say, the air particles will all travel to the top. It is just like in soda. The bubbles rise to the top as well. The gas wants be released and it is pressured to get out of the box."	3
good	0
"Sam could use the Gas bubble idea to support his claim. Gas bubbles are made up of particles. The gas bubbles float to the top of the can. So, the particles in the box will rise to the top also."	3
Sam will use the evidence given by his teacher to show that particles in any object or anything carbonated will all go to the top of that thing.C	0
Gas bubbles in soda float to the top when they are released from their airtight container.	0
He can use the soda example because it also rises to the top.	0
Sam could talk about how gas bubbles float to the top in a flat soda in his evidence. he could use this to support why he drew all the gas bubbles to the top.	3
He can use this by saying that gas bubbles float at the top of the soda	0
Pop the can of the soda.	0
"Sam thinks that the gas particles are in a drink, such as soda, making the particles go to the top."	0
that they all sray at the top because all are not at the top	0
The picture shows that gas floats to the top which is the same thing that gas bubbles do in soda.	3
"Sam could argue that a soda can is similar to a box of gas. If the gas bubbles float to the top in the soda, than that gas particles could do the same in a box of gas."	3
"Sam could use the example about soda, is the gas particles floating upwards, like gas bubbles in a can of soda."	3
Sam might use that gas bubbles float to the top because when you pour soda to a cup all the fuzz goes to the top.	0
Gas bubbles float to the top.	0
Sam might use this evidnce to support his claim that the particles are all at the top he might thinl they are oxgen.	0
"Same could say that when the gas particles of soda rise to the top, it will look like this."	3
gas float	0
"Sam might use the first piece of evidence, because it relates to gas particles and it states they float to the top."	0
he could pour some soda and watch the carbination float o the top.	0
He can support his claim saying that when you open any carbonated drinks the gas floats to the top.	0
sam might say something like oh my claim is correct because gas particles go to the top of the glass	0
That gas particles want to be released so they go to the top to get out of an area. For example a soda can.	0
cause they evaporte	0
because particles go to the ozone.	0
The best evidence is when we open bottle of soda all bubbles go top of bottle.	0
Sam might use the evidence to give example to support his claim in the best possible way.	0
The gas bubbles are like the gas particles.	0
Sam can try to explain that since particles and gas bubbles of soda are the same form of matter they will react the same way.	0
Sam says that since gas travels to the top of soda it must be the same for a box.	3
Particles move in the direction of going up.You can see when you open up a soda can.You can notice the bubbles and gas come out upward. which proves that particles move on the direction of going up.	0
How I think Sam might use any of this evidence to support his claim is that gas particles do indeed go to the top in soda as they float. So he can prove that it will sometimes go up.	3
"He might say that all gas bubbles in substances float to the top, based off of information."	0
"the gas would still be at the top at the end, but in the beginning, it would float to the top."	0
Sam can use both because because gas go up anyway	0
sam can use the example with the soda with all the air bubbles at the top to show that all air bubbles go to the top	3
Explain how the gas goes to fill in where it is like the carbonation goes to the top since that's the only way to get out of the can	0
Sam will use this to support his claim by showing what he drew and what gas bubbles do when placed in soda. He will say that gas bubbles float to the top in soda.	0
He will most likely use this evidence as an example to prove his point	0
because soda bubbles float to the top just like his picture	3
Sam might use his evidence to explain and show an example of how the soda bubbles float to the top just like how he thinks the gas particles will float to the top of the box after a minute.	3
that iin a can of soda the particles rise to the top and that in a baloon maybe they do too but its just appears that hey go to all directions.	0
"Sam may use the evidence, ""Gas bubbles in soda float to the top,"" in his argument because, like in his drawing the particles had been very close to the top end of his paper, meaning that the gas particles would have floated to the top."	3
Air rises and in a beverage so if air rises and even in drinks it must mean air will rise if contained too	0
Sam will use the soda evidence to support his claim since the thought the particles will rise.	0
Because the teacher said that gas bubbles in soda rise to the top	0
the gas will float to the top just like in sugar	0
Sam might use some of this information because it explains and says that the gas particles will stay on top and wont go in all directions.	0
"Sam can say that when carbon is trapped in a enclosed air tight space, once the air tight space is released, the carbon atoms float to the top."	0
Sam might use this evidence by saying that just because they go in different directions the balloon will still blow out.	0
The gas particles in sodas floats to the top so the ones in the box will too.	3
Gas bubbles rise to the top of soda.	0
"Sam would likely include the example of the soda because that one is the most like his drawing In his case he could mention the fact that the gas particles in soda rise, similar to the particles drawn in his example."	3
"Gas bubbles in soda float to the top, so the gas particles will float on the top too."	3
Sam will use the evidence of gas bubbles floating to the top to show how gas rises to one part.	0
When you blow air into a balloon it also goes to the top	2
Sam's evidence is that. idk	0
Well Gas bubbles in soda float up why not gas in a box	3
The gas bubbles float to the top. And so does the particles to Sam. That means his answer was right.	3
because he right	0
the gas bubbles rose in his	0
He might restate that the bubbles float to the top.	0
