review	label
Sam might say that the gas particles will float to the top like in a soda and it won't go in all directions because the box can't grow bigger.	3
"Sam could say that the soda shows that he is correct, because the gas in the soda floats to the top, just like he showed in his picture. He could also argue that because the balloon grows bigger in all directions, that means there are particles floating to the top."	3
"Sam could say that since the gas bubbles in soda will float to the top, that the gas particles in the box will float to the top as well."	3
he might say that when you open up a soda all of the bubbles are at the top not all around the soda	0
By showing it with a soda can.	0
Cause in a soda the gas goes to the top of the can	0
I think the why he can x	0
He will say that since his particles are gas particles and gas bubbles float to the top it will be the same for gas particles.	0
"In his claim, he said that gas particles will float to the top of the box. Gas bubbles in soda float to the top so he thinks that's what gas particles do after a minute."	3
He will use it to prove himself right.	0
"Gas will rise to the top, like how gas bubbles rise in soda. The gas bubbles can prove how the particles rise (In the viewpoint of Sam)."	3
Same evidence as in last part.	0
"For example, when you shake the soda bottle all of the gas bubbles move to the top."	0
"Sam might say ""The soda has gas in it when you open the can all the bubbles rise to the top, the same with the gas in the box."""	3
he might try to put that weird brain of his to work again.	0
all gas floats to the top	0
"Sam might use some of this evidence to support his claim that the particles are all at the top, by knowing that the gas bubbles in a soda float to the top of the bottle. Just like in his drawing all the gas particles are at the top."	3
"Sam thinking of soda when you open it, the gas would push the particles to the top. When you shake the bottle you could see the gas inside pushing the particles around the bottle."	0
gas always moves up	0
He could use this by saying the air in the balloons make the balloons float up. And that the gas floats all the way to the top.	2
"Just like how soda's gas bubbles float to the top, His picture show that the gas floats to the top. that's one piece of evidence that gas particles float to the top."	3
the gas particals in a ballon go up which it flyes away	0
"When the balloon expands , the gas particles don't stay still, and as shown in Sam's notebook they rise. This rise of these particles can be the reason of the expansion of a balloon."	2
"Sam might use this evidence by saying something like this.""My claim is that the gas particles will float to the top after one minute because, as my teacher explainded that gas bubbles in soda float to the top, just like gas particles will float to the top f the box."""	3
Sam will use the first piece of evidence regarding gas bubbles in soda floating to the top. He will use this piece of evidence because the way the teacher explains the gas particles' movement in that situation is the same as how the gas particles have moved in Sam's diagram.	3
sam might say in sod the bubbles go to the top then he might explain how that is similar to his theory about the box.	3
sam says the particles float up	0
because gas bubble s are almost same to the particles they go to the top just like sams claim.	3
"Sam could say something like this,gas particles travel upward because they have air bubbles that bring pockets of air up in gas particles."	0
Sam might use this evidence to re-think his argument.	0
Sam can use the the "Gas bubbles in soda float to the top" evidence since he thinks that the gas particles in the box rise to the top of the box.	3
This evidence can help out Sam because all gases move to the top	0
the particles go up just like a soda.	3
idk how to break it to him	0
"How I think that Sam's might use this claim is that he will say, when you open a soda you can see the gas bubbles float up cause they want to try to get out of the space"	3
"Sam would use the first piece of evidence that all the gas bubbles in soda float to the top because, theoretically, the bubbles in the container should do the same thint"	3
"Sam might say that both the soda and the box have gas particles in them, so the particles would react the same way in either place."	0
"I believe Sam would say the gas particles would rise to the top of the bx because according to the teacher, gas in a soda floats to the top."	3
Sam might use this evidence to support this claim: "Gas bubbles in soda float to the top."	0
Because gas rises	0
because carbonation goes up	0
"Sam can use the fact that when gas bubbles in soda float, they go to the top. He can claim that this will also happen with the gas particles in the experiment."	3
"""When you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions, but that's only happening when the object you are putting air in is move-able,"" Sam argued."	0
Sam can claim that gas bubbles float to the top in at least one form of gas he can draw diagrams to prove his claim is correct.	0
A good example is global warming. A explosion	0
Sam might use this because he would as that they grow bigger in all directions he might say that because its not clustered up in a single direction his is correct and he could also use the bubbles float in soda float to the top because its in uniform order at the top.	0
Sam might compare the evidence about the bubbles rising in soda to his claim that the particles rise to the top.	3
he could say that the balloons floats because all the helium gas floats up to the top of the balloon causing it to float and that the soda gas bubbles float because of a lower amount of oxygen in the bottle and all that gas	0
Sam might revisit the soda to prove that gas rises all together ans soda is just one example of this happening in the real world so that means that in all the gas will rise together and not spread out.	3
because when you pour a cup of soda all the bubbles rise to the top.	0
the balloon floats up when you use helium.	0
he would use this evidence and explain that gas floats to the top of the box because gas floats and goes to the top of whatever its contained in.	0
because when you open a soda the particles inside will float up gust like his claim said	0
Sam might say that balloons float to the top which means that the gas particle might be going up as well	2
Sam could use the evidence to support his claim because The teacher said that gas bubbles float to the top in soda which is what Sam drew in his notebook.	3
He could use this evidence about the gas bubbles from soda to explain why the particles went up at the same speed.	0
i think he will say that in a soda bubbles float to the top like particles	3
hell use that gas bubbles float to the top because thats what happened in his picture	0
Sam could say " since bubbles in a soda float to the top then the gas particles in a box must also float up."	3
according to gas bubbles they float to the top so he can use that.	0
"so if the bubbles in carbonated soda float to the top, all gases float to the top too."	3
sam could say that soda floats to the top so why cant gas particles do so	0
"Sam might use this info that his teacher gave him, by arguing that air particles float to the top, instead of being spread out."	0
They are all at the top and they are very high up in the sky and they all really loved it and some of the kids will all see in their birthday parties.	0
because GAS bubbles float to the top	0
When the teacher has not mentioned what type of gas it is in my head I imagined soda	0
"Say/write what he believes happens to gas for a minute, then say your evidence

REALITY OF SITUATION
Different gasses react in different situations"	0
His example is about soda	0
He'd probable say what I said previously about the bubbles floating to the top. He might also say something about the balloon rising or something and make a weak claim that it's because the air is rising or something	0
sam might you use any of the evidece because it does support his claim	0
I believe this because when you have a soda bottle the gas bubbles float to the top.	0
Because the effects of both could have possibly happened the same.	0
The gas is different than the one used in the balloon and the container is different	0
because of the soda bubbles	0
gas bubbles go up	0
Sam might use the evidence that the balloon might be filled wiht air not gas so it would be irrelevent to the topic.	0
Sam can use the evidence to support his claim because he can say that gas bubbles floating to the top because the air and gas particles are stuck inside it and are rising just as if it were being done in a room.	3
He might use that gas bubbles move to the top in soda so the particles in the box should to	3
"The gas bubbles float to the top when soda is poured into a cup. The same with gas particles, after a minuet the particles will rise to the top."	3
Sam might use this evidence to help his claim because he thinks that all the gas particles go to the top so he might say that just like a soda all the gas particles go to the top.	3
gas bubbles in soda float to the top	0
Sam might use the evidence to support his claim because the bubbles start from the bottom of the container and flow to the top like how they were at the bottom.	0
"Since gas is lighter and what the teacher said that the gas bubbles float to the top, water is denser and heavier, and the bubbles will try to float. It also depends on the type of gas you use. Helium which is lighter than air itself will float."	0
"Sam could say that just like how gas bubbles float to the top, the particles in the box all float to the top as well."	0
Sam thinks that the particles will float up to the top like bubbles in a soda.	3
just like soda air floats to the top well the same goes for balloons because when you blow the air into the balloon it goes to the top to make the balloon bigger	0
because the teacher told him what the particles might be	0
"The gas bubbles in the soda can make a fizz that only stays at the top of the can. So, maybe Sam could do an experiment supporting his claim."	0
Gas bubbles in soda float to the top	0
Sam might use any of this evidence to support his claim that the particles are all at the top because according to the teacher the soda bubbles go up to the top and the soda bubbles are gas.	3
"Since soda has air, why wouldn't it work normally."	0
The gas goes up	0
Sam could use this evidence because it shows what they believe.	0
"The bubbles in soda go to the top, which means gas particles do too."	3
Sam used this evidence cause the particles are cold	0
The teacher helps Sam by telling him that bubbles in soda float to the top. So Sam thinks that his claim is correct.	0
"Sam might use the evidence where gas bubbles in soda float to the top, because that would be the same thing that he drew on his notebook. Sam said that all of the gas particles will stay together and only move, or float up to the top, while the teacher said that the gas particles in a soda will float to the top."	3
He uses that gas bubbles in soda float to the top since his picture explains exactly what is happening.	3
He would say just like the soda all particles go up.	0
Sam's evidence was when you open a soda bottle the gas in it floats up.	0
He used the evidence that the bubbles in the soda float up to draw the particles floating up.	0
He might say that when you open a soda it goes up. But you have to blow the gas.	0
Sam is correct because the gas particles float to the top: Gas particles float to top.	0
"Since Sam's claim said that the gas particles were at the top, then the evidence he would use is what matches his claim."	0
His Claim is right if it is soda	0
Sam might use the evidence that the gas bubbles in soda float to the top so they can evaporate.	0
"Soda bubbles float to the top, so gas particles would go up too."	3
Sam might analogize that the box is the cup and the bubbles are the gas particles.	0
"Sam might use the first piece of information to explain his drawing where all the gas particles spread to the top. By using the part of the statement that says that the bubbles in the soda float to the top, he could argue that the gas particles went to the top in the same way."	3
"Sam might use this evidence to explain, that similar to the bubbles in a soda can, which flow up when they are shaken. This is what Sam claims, which was in her drawing."	3
"Sam could use both pieces of evidence to support his claim that the particles are at top. The particles inside, a balloon are gas particles, and they go in all directions, which includes the top. Whereas, the gas bubbles are also gas particles which float to the top. This matches with Sam's model, as he ""drew"" the particles near the top."	3
"Sam will use, the teacher example's of the gas bubbles in soda floating to the top. This is because this correspondents with his claim, the gas particles float to the top."	0
"Sam might use the ""Gas bubbles in the soda float to the top"" information in order to support his claim because if the gas in the soda floats to the top, the gas in the box will float to the top too."	3
Sam used the first evidence because he claimed that the gas particles will float up to the top near each other.	0
"When you open up a soda can, the gas bubbles come all the way to the top. This is similar to his picture because it also represents the gas molecules going to the top."	3
Sam uses the evidence that the gas bubbles in soda float to the top because in his claim he said that the particles went up.	3
"Also, the balloon gets bigger on top, so that also shows gas going up. Sodas, gas also moves upward."	3
The air in the balloon might float to the top and expand the top of the box a little while the other sides are still the same.	0
He might use this information by relating the diagram to the example.	0
"Sam drew that all the gas particles floated to the top. The teacher stated that gas bubbles in soda float to the top. This correlates with what Sam thinks, only instead of a soda can, they're just in a box."	3
Sam can say that the image of the particles at the top of the box represent the bubbles at the top of the soda.	0
Sam might use any of this evidence to support his claim by saying that soda's bubbles rise up to the top.	0
"Sam could argue that the gas is inside of soda. If not, however, he doesn't have any evidence."	0
Sam could use this evidence to support his claim because when you blow out the particles go to the top.	0
Sam could've used this information to say that the gas molecules were the ones in the soda because they float up	0
Sam would use the evidence that gas bubbles in soda float to the top because he showed that the gas particle floated to the top of the container.	3
The gas bubbles in soda float to the top and so did the gas particles he drew.	3
Sam will use the first piece of evidence because he claimed the particles are going to the top and are compact.	0
"Sam might use the evidence that gas bubbles in soda float up to the top.
He might use this because gas bubbles in a soda will float to the top when they are shaken or air is let in."	0
The gas will flout because the gas is lightweight or maybe it's warmer.	0
Sam could use the gas bubbles floating to the top because his gases floated twords the top of the box.	3
That when you blow on them then they will move to the top because they are in liquid. Both evidence could support his claim.	0
Sam might use this evidence to support his claim that the particles are all at the top since the gas bubbles float to the top in soda.	3
"Sam would argue that there would already be a fluid in the container, and that it would be more dense than the air bubbles forcing the bubbles upward."	0
