review	label
He would say just like the balloon all particles will float around.	1
When you blow up a balloon the gas on it going in all directions.	1
He might say that soda moves to one spot because it is filled with carbonated water put in the air the gas is all around us.	0
"When you blow air into a balloon, the balloons grow bigger in all directions.
."	0
It makes sense in any way	0
"Charlie could use the second piece of evidence, as he drew gas particles spreading out."	1
"Balloons inflate in all directions, so gas particles would spread out too."	2
Charlie might analogize that the box is the balloon and the air blown in are the gas particles.	0
"Charlie might use the second piece of information to explain his drawing where all the gas particles spread out in all directions. By using the part of the statement that says that the balloon grows bigger in all directions, he could argue that the gas particles spread in all directions in the same way."	2
"Charlie, might use his evidence to explain, that similar to the bubbles in a balloon, which spread apart as the balloon is blown up. This was Charlie's claim."	1
"Charlie could use the second piece of evidence to support his claim that the particles are all around the container, as the gas particles in a balloon spread out in direction, which causes the balloon to become bigger."	2
"Charlie will use, the teachers example of when you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions. This is because charlie's claim stated that gas particles spread out wide, and take the space of the container."	2
"Charlie might use ""when you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions."" He will use this because if the gas molecules cause the balloons to expand in all directions, then the gas must be everywhere, so it will also be everywhere in the box."	0
Charlie will use the second evidence because he claimed that the particles will be all spread out around the space and not clustered together	2
"Charlie may use piece of evidence because when you blow up a balloon, it gets bigger and bigger, making the molecules spread out much more."	1
"Charlie uses the evidence that when you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions because the particles disperse in his claim."	2
"The soda's gas would also make a balloon spread out, because the gas will move around."	1
Charlie might say that the box might expand its sides a little from the air spreading inside.	0
"The gas particles are all around the container. The teacher stated that when you blow air into a balloon, it grows bigger in all directions, which means there is air in all directions. That is exactly what Charlie said, only in a container, not a balloon."	0
Charlie can say that the particles spread out in the image represent the particles when the balloon expands.	2
"Charlie could argue that the gas is in a balloon. If not, there's no way to prove his point."	0
Charlie could say that the particles float to the top but then also spread out to the sides.	0
"Charlie could've said that the molecules were pushed out like the ones in the balloons, so his evidence is accurate."	2
Charlie would use the evidence that balloons grow bigger in all directions when air is blown into it. The air in the container would spread out in all directions too.	2
If the balloon grows in all directions then the gas molecules go in all directions like how Charlie drew them.	2
"Charlie would use the second piece of evidence because he claimed that all the particles will be spread out and all around the space, which the evidence supports."	0
"Charlie might use the evidence that when you blow air into the balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions.
He might use this because gas particles spread out when air is let in."	2
Charlies bubbles spread out in diffrent directions and so does the gas in the ballons.	2
Charlie will use the evidence stating that the container is like the balloon and that the air is like the breath. It supports his claim.	0
Charlie might use any of this evidence to support his claim that the particles are all around the container since his claim is the gas particles go in all directions the same as the balloon's gas particles.	2
Charlie would argue that the container was empty and the gas would expand to fill it. This would cause it to increase in size.	0
He can prove that the surface was covered with air .And that makes sense.	0
That when you blow in a blown the particles skaters every where	1
when you blow up a balloon the gas bubbles fill the balloon and make it expand outwards.	1
that they has gas so they go where ever they want	0
He will explain the fact that particles in balloons go in random directions just like his diagram.	2
i dont know how to discribe him	0
"Yes, when you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions."	0
Charlie could use this evidence to say that particles spread	0
The balloon.	0
"Charlie can use this evidence that when you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all direction."	0
The particles will act like the balloon.	0
Charlie might use the evidence to support his saying that the gas particles in a balloon are all spread out. He also might use it in a paragraph or essay.	2
charlie use his claim the in a balloon the gas goes in every direction	1
when you blow into a balloon it gets bigger as you keep blowing and the particles are moving around.	1
he could also say the teacher was his source	0
maybe he will think that the sugar will not go in the middle.	0
that is more gas particles	0
"Charlie can use the evidence when you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions and he could say that his claim is correct too because his teacher explained how gas particles in balloons spread throughout all the directions."	2
"Since in a balloon gas particles spread apart, so can the gas particles in the box."	2
Charlie is correct because after a while the particles spread out.	0
he will say that since the ballon grew the particals spread	1
"Charlie should use the balloon evidence because, this supports his claim of gas spreading around."	2
"""When you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions."" Charlie will use this as evidence since nothing else backs up his claim about what the gas particles will do. I have no idea if I'm correct that Sam is right but at least I tried knowing practically nothing on this topic."	2
Charlie is gonna fail.	0
the gas in a balloon doesnt go up it goes all the way.	1
Charlie would use the balloon evidence to show that the particles are spaced out.	2
"Charlie might use the evidence that when you blow air in a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions."	0
"He could use the balloons expand in all direction by saying that the gas particles would react similarly to how they do in a balloon, expanding in all directions."	2
the particles spread like air.	0
"Charlie may say, when blowing air into a balloon it expands from all side, so when one minute passes, the gas particles will part from one another. It'll soon expand and show that the gas particles is causing movement inside the box."	2
Because in his drawing he says that the gas particles are moving around constantly which proves that the balloon is getting bigger when you blow into it.	0
Charlie might use this evidence to show how all the particles are moving around in different spots.	0
just like how the gas in balloons goes in all directions the gas in this box is in all directions	2
Charlie might use this evidence by saying gas bubbles travel in all different directions like a balloon being filled with air.	2
"hes using a balloon as evidence, to show that when you blow into a balloon the air inside expands so that must be what the gas particles are doing."	1
He can also say that this type of air is found in balloons.	1
gas particle will fill in all the space in the box because in a balloon the the air will expand.	2
Charlie might use this information because the balloon got bigger and the particles expanded around the container.	2
"Charlie will use the evidence that the air in a balloon spreads out in all directions, because that is very similar to his explanation of how particles move in a container. He will relate the air particles to the particles in a container by saying that they are both gas, and therefore, they act in a similar way."	2
The gas of the outside pushes the water to the sides to create more mass on the water and it spread to get an even taste.	0
Because the gas particles will get bigger and go in all directions	0
he can use the evidence by saying the gas just expands it is all over the place	0
Charlie might use this evidence to support his claim because the illustration refers to the balloon analogy.	0
Charlie can use his evidence to support his cliam by sayin the particles need to go cray	0
He could use this to explain how since the box is empty the air particles could spread instead of stay together.	1
That if you blow up a balloon the gas particles move around making the balloon go any direction just like the particles inside the box.	2
Charlie could use this example of the balloon to reason an explanation or a hypothesis on what the gas particles do in one minute.	0
he could use the evidence that states balloons get bigger in all directions	0
He might say that there is different ways to say that the gas is moving around and also include the evidence that was stated by his teacher.	1
it's also very important.	0
"He might say that all air is is gas and if the balloon expands with the air, the gas particles expand."	1
he could say his drawing gas particals in a balloon when it is blown.	0
Charlie can use this evidence to support his claim by telling me how the effect of the balloon and how you blow it can also happen with the gas particles but instead of air its gas.	1
"Soda is a liquid and the gas floats to the top because it is lighter. However, the balloon does not contain liquid and neither does the box."	0
"Now, Charlie knows that a balloon expands when you breath air into it, so he knows gas particles expand, so he is correct."	1
because it is free all around.	0
"I think Charlie can use the evidence that when you blow air into a balloon, the balloon gets bigger in all directions to support his claim."	0
that the particles have more mass they will go apart.	0
Charlie might use any of this evidence because his particles are going in all directions and some of his gas particles are on the top of hi diagram.	0
Charlie might use the evidence that air blown into a balloon will make a balloon grow bigger in all directions because his drawing shows particles that are spread out.	1
To prove what particles will do in a balloon filled w/ air.	0
This can support Charlie's claim because when air spreads all around in a balloon when you blow it up his diagram show the air spreading around too like i a balloon.	2
"Charlie's evidence showed that air particles go farther apart as they are heated, by the breath of whoever is blowing the balloon."	0
"Since when you blow air into a balloon all the particles spread out, that is how Charlie could use this as evidence. Your breath is ho, so when you blow into a balloon you are blowing heat onto the particles, making them spread out, just like on Charlie's picture."	2
Particles in a balloon scatter out to have more space.	1
Charlie can also use the evidence cause it also supports his claim.	0
because he showed that.	0
Charlie can image that the box is the balloon and the dots are the particle in which the balloon grows because to make the balloon bigger of the pressure of the air we blow into the balloon. And the particles move in all direction.	2
"that when the soda is just placed there, the particles are just like charlies"	0
I think that Charlie's drawing is the little particles everywhere because there is a huge amount of space in the box even without the air of your breath.	0
Charlie would say the since the balloon grows on all sides then the gas must be spread out so his claim must be correct	1
"Charlie's claim is that the particles are all spread out around the box. The evidence that when you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows larger in all directions relates to Charlie's claim. Charlie thinks the same thing is happening to the gas particles in the box. This evidence shows that since the air in the balloon spread out, the gas particles in the box may do the same."	2
"I think Charlie might use this evidence to support his claim by saying, since if you blow air into a balloon, it expands in all directions, so if you give time to have the particles move, it will spread out throughout the box in all directions, using the evidence,""When you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions."""	2
Charlie might say that the balloon is getting bigger because the air is pushing it outwards in all directions.	1
"if it wasn't all around, balloons wouldn't inflate."	0
because when you blow air into a balloon the particles go everywhere maybe this too	2
charlie will use the balloon evidence since it is similar to his drawing he will say that if the box was a balloon the molecules would bounce around the walls and bounce on themselves	2
when you blow into a balloon the gas particles goes everywhere	1
"the evidence that when balloons are blown up that the air in it spreads out and makes the balloon expand, supports the claim that when air is traped in a box the air would naturaly spread out"	2
He could use it to say that his claim is like blowing up a balloon where the particles spread out throughout the balloon.	2
"I think charlie will try and do the same thing as Sam, so he will support his claim and prove wrong other claims."	0
"The gas particles in a balloon expand, so the gas particles normally go around"	2
Charlie might use any of this evidence to support his claim because if balloon particles spread out then so do particles.	2
He might use the evidence his teacher told him to help other people know what his diagram is about and a example of were it can be used.	0
cause they move to the peices around	0
"I think Charlie might think when you blow air into a balloon the gas particles will float all around making the balloon bigger, so the gas particles in a box will probably also do that but instead of making the box bigger, it will stay the same."	0
Charlie might use this evidence to support his claim because a balloon has gas particles everywhere (making sure it's not deflated) just like his sketch.	2
"Charlie might the when you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions evidence to support his claim that the particles are all around the container."	2
"Charlie might use this evidence to support his claim because when you blow a balloon, it goes in all different directions just like it did in his diagram."	2
"He may use the balloon evidence to say, my particles will spread out too."	2
Charlie could say that the particles in the balloon could be used to be used for the his model.	1
"Charlie will use the ""when you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger"" evidence because when you do blow air into a balloon, it expands in every single direction that it will be able to."	1
Charlie might use the fact that gas particle spread out as a balloon is inflated.	2
"Charlie can use any of this evidence to support his claim because his claim was that gas particles move all around the container, and the carbonated bubbles in soda move all around in the glass."	2
"Charlie might use the evidence that when you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions because his particles are spaced out randomly."	2
"Charlie might use this evidence to support his claim because he argued that the gas particles will spread out evenly. If the balloon spreads out in all directions, that basically means the air is spreading out the way Charlie's model shows."	2
"Charlie might use any of this evidence to support his claim by saying that air in a balloon goes in all directions, like his diagram"	2
the balloon had blow aired	0
because the particles go everywhere	0
