review	label
Charlie will use the evidence provided by his teacher to show that particles any objects like balloons scatter around inside of the object at different paces and in different places.	2
The balloon is filled with air and grows in all directions as it is filled.	0
"Charlie might included the fact that when you blow air into a balloon, the gas particles move everywhere. that could explain why he drew gas partcles all over the place."	2
"Charlie thinks that the gas particles are in the air in general, such as a balloon, making the particles spread out."	2
they all should have the same distance	0
The picture shows that gas floats around which is what happens when you blow in a balloon. When you blow into a balloon the balloon expands in all directions.	0
"Charlie could use this evidence to argue that a balloon is similar to a box of gas. If the gas particles spread out in the balloon, than the same effect could be expected from the box."	2
"Charlie can use the example about the balloon because he drew his particles spread out, like a balloon when it is being blown up."	2
"Charlie might use that when you blow air into a balloon, it grows bugger in all direction."	0
Air in a balloon is evenly distributed inside it.	1
gas disperse	0
"Charlie might use the second piece of evidence, because it mentions how the balloon grows bigger in all directions which matches his prediction about gas particles."	0
when you blow air in a balloon air particles spread to fill it.	1
He can use this evidence saying that when you blow air in a balloon the gas goes everywhere.	1
That gas particles want space so the fill up an area.	0
gas gas couild go everywhere	0
because some of them split.	0
The best evidence is when we blow balloon it grows bigger all direction.	0
Charlie will use this evidence to give example to show that he might be right	0
"Charlie could say that since matter is all around us, the particles have to be spread out like a blown up balloon."	1
Charlie says since the gas tries to spread out in a balloon there should be no difference between the gas in the box than in the balloon.	2
Can you blow up a balloon by just having the particles with in it upwards. Enable for a balloon to be blown up in needs gas/particles within it all over/around the balloon.	1
"How Charlie might use this evidence to support his claim that the particles are all around the container is that when you blow a balloon, it expands in all directions. So, depending on the situation, gas particles will sometimes go all around an enclosed space."	2
the gas expanded to the open spaces in the soda.	0
Charle can use both because gas came up anyway	0
charlie can use the balloon example to show that air particles go in all directions because the air inside the balloon is going in all directions	1
He can explain that the gas goes to fill up the space it's being put in	1
Charlie will use the piece of evidence that supports his claim of gas particles spreading out in a balloon.	2
because his gas particles are all spread out just how it would be if you blew into a balloon	2
Charlie might use his evidence to show that when you blow a balloon the air will float all around the balloon just like how he thinks that the gas particles will float around the entire box after waiting for one minute.	2
"that the particles in soda rise because of the liquid that puts pressure on them and that the particles have air in them so the air in the particles makes them float to the top, but in the box there is no liquid, also that in a ballon the particles fill the baloon up equally in the middle and the sides, if it went just to the top there would be a crease in the middle."	0
"Charlie may use the evidence, ""When you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions,"" in his argument because, his own drawing had particles much more spread out, like a balloon as a blows up as it air particles are spreading out and pushing out trying to fill in the empty space."	2
Balloons grow in a circle even and so it means that gas takes the shape that its contained in meaning the particles in the air in the box should be spread out taking the form of the shape its in	2
Charlie can use the balloon evidence to support his claim since he thought the particles will spread out.	2
Because the teacher said that when you blow air into a balloon it gets bigger	0
the gas will blow and spread just like a balloon	1
"Because the particles he drew represent air, and since his teacher said him that when you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions, he might think he is right."	2
"Charlie can stay that when you blow oxygen in a open flexible space, atoms can move more freely."	0
He might say that particles are smaller than bubbles and you can still see the little bubbles throughout the soda not just at the top.	0
In a balloon the gas spreads out.	1
"When balloons grow, the gas particles spread in all directions, exactly as Charlie's were drawn."	2
Particles is all around the container like balloon and makes the balloon bigger.	0
Charlie will use the evidence of the air in a balloon expanding in all directions to show how gas spreads our all around the container.	2
When you blow air into a balloon it also goes to the top	0
He probably used this because a box is like a balloon and the box is kinda of like a balloon	0
"Charlie must also think that hes right, because his answer was correct as well. The air goes all over the balloon."	1
because he is right	0
"Charlie would explain that the balloon is growing in all different directions and that if the particles only floated to the top, only the top part of the balloon would grow. Since all parts of the balloon are growing. the particles must be spread out."	0
Charlie might say that the gas particles will spread like a balloon and it won't rise because there's no soda.	0
"Charlie could say that since the balloon and its particles spread out in all directions, then the gas particles must spread out too."	2
he might say that the balloon has air all throughout the balloon	1
Cause he thinks they go all around the soda can	0
He will use the fact that air particles make a balloon go in all directions so it probably is the same for gas particles.	1
He will use it to prove himself right.	0
"When you inflate a balloon, it doesn't expand in one direction, it grows in all directions. Gas will move in all directions, and you can see that happening in a balloon (In viewpoint of Charlie)."	2
Same evidence as in last part.	0
"Charlie can use this evidence because just like his chart, the particles will grow bigger in all directions. So if he blows into the balloon, the particles will grow bigger."	0
He can be smart and think on his own. he doesnt need evidence	0
Charlie might use some of this evidence to support his claim that the particles are all around the container by knowing that the when you blow air into a balloon the balloon grows bigger in all directions. Since in his drawing it had shown that the particles are going in all different directions.	2
"Charlie's claim is when you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions. That means the particles in the balloon with the gas is going moving the particles to different places inside the balloon."	1
that gas always moves	0
I think he can only use the one where the balloon can get bigger in all directions because that is close to representing his claim.	0
Gas spreads out in all directions. Just like how when you're blowing up a balloon it expands and grows bigger in all directions. His picture shows the gas particles spreading out in all directions.	2
"Charlie might say something like this.""My claim is that after one minute the gas particle will be all over the place,because as my teacher said when you blow a balloon, the balloon grow bigger in all direction just like my claim that all the particle will go in all directions."""	2
Charlie will use the second piece of evidence regarding the expansion of a balloon when air is blown into it. He will use this piece of evidence because the way the teacher explains the gas particles' movement in that situation is the same as how the gas particles have moved in Charlie's diagram.	1
charlie might explain how a balloon gets bigger from the gas inside because they are everywhere then he will tell how that is related to his bow theory.	1
charlie says that the particles are all seperated from each other	0
because charlie thinks that they may go to the middle and when you blow a balloon all that air that you blow into it. it goes everywhere	1
"Charlie could something like this,gas particles travel outward because they don't have much air to bring them to the top so the expand instead."	0
Charlie might use this evidence to brain storm his theory.	0
"Charlie can use the ""When you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions"" sentence as his evidence, because he believes that the gas inside of the box goes in all directions after a minute."	2
charlie can use this evidence to help because when the gases move up they float round everywhere	0
when your blowing a balloon it expands fills all space it can	1
"Charlie would say that when you fill a balloon, the gas scatters and goes everywhere, so the gas in the container should as well."	2
Charlie might say that the box has air and gas particles in it and when you blow air into a balloon air and gas particles are entering the balloon so the particles will do the same thing.	2
They can also be spread around.	0
balloons go out in all directions.	0
"Charlie, using the evidence that the teacher says about balloons, can claim that it acts like a balloon, spreading out in all directions."	1
Charlie can use this evidence to prove his point by showing there are different ways that gas particles can float.	0
charlie might use the evidence that the ballon grows in diffrent directions and he claims that the gas particles were all in differnt directions	0
A explosion is a similar effect.	0
Charlie might use the evidence about the balloon and share that his picture is more accurate because it shows the gas particles spread out and he could use the soda one because he could state that the gas particles are going up.	1
Charlie might compare the evidence about the air making the balloon expand in all directions to his claim that the particles expand in all directions.	2
"there are usually a few gas bubbles at the top and around sides of glass of coke when you pour into a cup, and the balloon blows in all directions to fill up properly so what's not to say that there arengas particles too that blow into all directions"	2
Charlie might use the balloon and the soda as an example saying that the gas spreads out when not held back by a liquid so everywhere that is not underwater will have gas spreding out and not clumping together.	1
because when you blow a balloon the gasses are every where	1
They are floating up while they are spreading out in the box.	0
he might use evidence to explain that gas can float anywhere and when contained it will go everywhere	0
when you get a balloon the particles inside will spread out expanding the balloon	1
Charlie might say that the soda is a chilled beverage and what happens during carbonation and not when the gas particles heat up	0
Charlie could use any of this evidence to support his claim because the teacher said that the air in a balloon goes in all directions including center which is what Charlie said.	2
Charlie could use this evidence about the balloon to explain why the particles may be from a balloon and so explain why they went up at a different speed.	0
i think he will say that they will spread out like air does to a balloon	1
hell use that particles fly everywhere because thats what happened in his drawing	0
"all particles bounce around, and they will keep bouncing. the bouncing spreads out all the gas particles."	0
"Charlie might use this information that his teacher gave him, to argue that air particles spread out to fill up all the empty space in the box."	0
"Bubbles even have gas and they pop it when kids touch it, or popped it to the ground and some of the little kids will play bubbles or adults will play it and kids would pop it."	0
because air particles stay at the same spot	0
As though the teacher did not mention what type of gases she/he was referring too the gas i thought of was the kin of when you blow into a ballon and particles spread.	1
Charlie could use this evidence because in his picture the particles are all around the container and in the balloon the particles moving all around the container make it expand.	2
his is about a ballon	0
Charlie would probably say the same thing I said earlier about gas going in all directions in a balloon. He might also make a claim that bubbles rising is different due to the difference in mass from water to gas.	2
he will probloby way just use one of the picecs of evidence	0
Because the effects of both could have possibly happened the same.	0
The gas in the balloon only has one way out but there is more gas coming from there so it is spreading.	1
because of the blowing air into a ballon type of thing	0
gas spreads out	0
Charlie might say that gas in that form is different then gas in another form.	0
Charlie can use his evidence because he can say the way air goes into the balloon and spreads around inside just as if the gas particles were in a room.	2
Since particles in a balloon spread out so should they	2
"When blowing up a balloon, the balloon will begin to expand in all directions. Same with gas particles, after a minuet the gas particles will begin to expand everywhere."	1
Charlie might use this evidence to help his claim because he thinks that all the gas particles will go all over the place so he might say that sense you blow air into a balloon and all the gas particles go all over the place.	2
"when you blow into a balloon, the balloons grow bigger in all directions."	0
Charlie might use any of this evidence to support his claim because the particles try to fill up the entire box like how the particles in a balloon try to fill up all space in the balloon.	2
"Air is affected by gravity, which means that the particles are being pushed down or floating not so high of a distance. That's why you need an air pump to go to someplace high like Mt.Everest."	0
Charlie might use the evidence of the balloon and the air by saying the gas particles in the box spread all around the box just like how the air in a balloon spreads when the balloon is being blown.	2
Charlie thinks that the particles will spread out like a balloon.	1
because the paarticles are everywhere now	0
"The gas in an air balloon goes in all different directions and fills it up completely. Charlie could an experiment, like Sam, to support his claim."	1
gas rises so he thinks hes right.	0
"When you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions"	0
Charlie might use any of this evidence to support his claim that the particles are all around the container because when you blow up a balloon it grows bigger in all directions.	0
"In balloon, the air spreads in all directions, and since the balloon has is air, why wouldn't it work the same in normal conditions?"	1
The gas goes to the sides	0
Charlie could use this evidence because it shows what they believe.	0
The air in a balloon (when being blown up) expands the balloon. Which means the gas particles go everywhere.	1
"Charlie might use the evidence where the balloon grows bigger in all directions if you blow air into it, because he drew an image related to this evidence in his notebook. Charlie said that the particles of gas will break apart from each other and spread out in the box, while the teacher also said that the balloon grows bigger in all directions, which is like saying that the gas particles will spread out in all directions."	2
He uses that when you blow air into a balloon the balloon grows bigger in all direction since his picture is explaining it all	2
