review	label
she can just do what she side to do	0
"This evidence could be used to support Charlieå«s claim by showing how the gas particles would go in all directions, not just the top."	0
When the gas bubbles go to the top it is like the balloon gets bigger.	0
"When you blow a balloon, it has helium to make it bigger."	0
t h a t g l a s s p a r t i c l e s s p r e a d l i k e a i r .	0
"When blowing air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions, supports Charlie's claim because when one minute has pasted, Charlie believes that the gas particles will distant from the box and separate from one another. When blowing air into a balloon, the balloon expands, Charlie is saying that the box may expand when the gas particles part."	2
Because the gas particles spread all around which makes the balloon grow.	1
This evidence explains Charlie's claim because the particles are moving all over in the balloon like in his picture.	2
because the gas is in all directions like a ballone	1
The evidence can support Charlie's claim because when you blow into a balloon there's heat which makes the particles move. It's like heat is the energy for the particles.	0
the teacher is trying to say the the particals are speading out and that is was the image shows us	0
the bubble want every were	0
This could help Charlie's claim because when a balloon is being filled with air it grows bigger in all directions just like the gas bubbles	0
This evidence explains that the sugar in the water is going in one direction but is also spreading.	0
hes saying that when you blow air into a balloon the air in the balloon expands making it bigger then that must be that the gas particles are doing.	1
This evidence helps Charlie because it says what type of air it might be	0
the gas particles will expand filling all the space like balloon	1
It could be used because it went in all directions.	0
This supports his claim because he depicts the gas particles spred out and a balloon filled with gas spreds out on all sides	2
This evidence can also support Charlies claim because it supports charlies claim of the gas particles sepreating from one another	0
"This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim because he could relate the particles in a balloon and the particles in a container, by saying that just like the air in a balloon move farther apart, and spread out in all directions when you blow into it, particles in a container spread out in all directions as well."	2
When you blow a balloon up the particles are not in one area but every where in the balloon.	1
Charlie can use this as a supporting detail because the image above shows that the sugar pieces are still floating but are spread out away from each other. This happens also when you blow a balloon. They spread apart making the air expand in the balloon eventually making more space int he balloon (before it eventually pops).	2
The air moved the sugar particles into different directions to help the sweet flavor spread.	0
because the air could go all derections or it will pop if it went one way only.	0
When you blow a balloon the gas particles will get bigger when you blow into a balloon.	1
it helps explain because its basically saying that the bubbles go all different types of ways.	0
"This can support the claim because, it mentions that the balloon grows bigger in all in directions and Charlie drew the gas particles floating around the box."	1
"This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim because his claim is that the particles did not rise to the top but rather randomly, and the balloon grows bigger by the air going in all the directions just like Charlie's claim."	2
"This supports Charlie's claim because her gas particles are going in every direction, just like the teacher explained the balloon."	2
the teacher tells charlie that the balloon expands in all directions.	0
Charlie's illustration demonstrates the gas bubbles expanding in all directions like the balloon.	2
when you a balloon the air goes in all directions to make the balloon bigger	1
This evidence will help support charlie's claim because the particles in the balloon go all over the place to make the balloon bigger.	1
this can be used to support charlies claim because he can be correct	0
This could help Charlie's claim because the gas particles are more spread out therefore they grow bigger of all directions	0
"It could support his claim because it would explain how when you blow a balloon the air particles spread out instead of stay in one solid spot. Therefore, the air particles will spread out after one minute."	1
This can help because it says how the air is going in different directions and all over the place.	0
This evidence supports charlies claim because he says that the gas spreads out and the teacher says that when you blow up a balloon the balloon grows on all sides.	1
this explains how the gas bubbles expand into the box	0
That since you blow up a ballon the gas particles move around everywhere to make the balloon bigger.	1
I think that the air is spreading out to take more room and be much bigger in mass not like soda where it wants to get out and pop and not explode where air wants to take all the air it can.	0
Because when you blow up and air balloon the air goes n all different directions trying to fill up the balloon.	1
He could explain how balloons get bigger in all directions could also happen in a box	0
in his claim it says that the particles are all over the place and that a balloon does the same	2
"When you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions and air goes every where"	1
This evidence supports Charlie's claim because he can say that the particles are moving everywhere stretching out the balloon making it bigger. This can be used but you have to put details.	1
it looks like there is a lot of particles.	0
it show that the molkls sptto dissover	0
"A blown balloon, expands and the balloon has gas particles and for the reason for the balloon expanding is that the gas particle are spreading out."	1
"This explain Charlies evidence because the teacher said that when you blow air into the balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions and thats what charlies said."	1
this could help him cause if in a baloon they flot all around then way wont it do the same here	2
the gas particles had energy going everywhere.	0
This supports Charlie's claim as in the picture the gas particles are are going all over the place just like what happens when air is filled into a balloon.	2
This can prove his claim because the gas particals in his drawing could be gas particals in a balloon when it is blown.	1
hit soused poues his evidence by exspouing the bobbles	0
This evidence can support Charlie by telling him that how you blow into a balloon can also happen with the gas particles but with gas.	0
The gas just doesn't fill up one spot it fells up all spots weather its at once or not it fells up all spots.	0
"Because air particles go ever where in a balloon ,they would do the same in a box."	2
"When you add air into a balloon, the air travels to different areas which inflates the balloon, making it expand."	1
The air he blows into the ballon mixes with all the other gas particles and mixes around	1
Because if you know that body temp of human is 88 degree celcius. and if you blow a balloon the air particle in you mouth will bounce around inside the balloon because air particle will goes crazy if it has high temp	1
"Since the balloon becomes bigger when you blow more air into it, that means the gas particles spread out more to expand the balloon, so this means Charlie is correct."	1
the teacher is right because the picture	0
because the particles are all free in the balloon.	0
"The evidence that ""When you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions."" supports Charlie's claim because his claim was that the gas particles will spread out."	2
This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim because when you blow a balloon the balloon will get bigger and bigger which the balloon grows bigger in all directions and Charlie drew that the gas particles will move in all direction and it will spread out.	1
they have more mass.	0
This evidence could be used to support Charlie‰Ûªs claim because the object was not named and the particles in his picture are spread apart from each other in different directions.	0
That could support Charlie's claim because he drew his gas particles in all directions and Charlie's teacher says that when you blow air into a balloon it grows bigger in every direction so that shows that what his teacher said can be used as information for Charlie's claim.	2
"'- by saying ""When you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions.‰Û"	0
all the partacils will start to move faster in the ballone because the hot air in your mouth will go in the ballone	0
This evidence can support Charlieå«s claim because it an example of particles spreading out.	0
because hot air moves faster because you use hot air to fill up a ballon	0
It can support Charlies claim because it shows that gas particles spread everywhere.	0
"The fact that when air is blown into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions supports Charlie's claim because the gas particles will move with the balloon in all directions."	1
"This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim by showing that in some cases, the gas particles are spread out. This could be because of what type of gas particles are being put into it."	0
This can be supported because the particle moves up and around in a balloon more when the space inside is greater.	0
This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim because when you blow up a balloon the air spreads all around the balloon causing each side of the balloon to grow and raise just like how Charlie's diagram shows the particles spreading all around.	2
"Evidence we could use to support Charlie's claim of,‰ÛÏWhen you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions.‰Û We could say that it as air particles spread apart over an elapsed period of time. They also rise up."	1
"Since a balloon grows bigger when you blow air into it, it shows that this could be what is happening on Charlie's picture. When you blow air inside a balloon, the air entering the balloon is hot. This causes all the particles to spread out, just like on Charlie's picture."	2
"The air in a balloon is scattered out, just like in Charlie's claim."	2
Charlie's claim is also correct because they spread out in all directions and the Science teacher admitted that too.	0
Because Charlie showed particle going in all directions.	0
"Since his diagram shows the molecules expanding, of at least in motion, and hitting all the walls, the same principle would apply to the balloon, and that would support his claim, that the balloon is doing what his diagram shows."	2
this evidence could be used to support charlies claim because he could argue that the particles in the box want to be spread out like when you blow air into a balloon.	2
Charlie can say that the box is a balloon and the particles move in all direction than moving up. This make to balloon grow bigger because of all the directions of the particles.	2
"this could be supported by having a balloon and you blow the balloon up, the whole thing becomes larger not just one part."	1
"I think this evidence could be supported to Charlies claim, because Charlie drew the gas particles spread apart, and the teacher tells him that,the balloon grows bigger in all directions. This means that the gas particles in the balloon spread apart."	2
"When you blow a balloon the little particles float around because your breath put air in it and you breath have more mass than the balloon, so if you blow up a balloon the little particle float everywhere and spreads out."	1
"If Sam's claim were true then the gas in balloon would rises and the balloon would be less like a sphere and more like a tube with the gas at the top, instead the gas is spread out and makes the balloon the shape that it is."	1
"This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim because his particles are all over the place after a minute. And after a minute of blowing a balloon, the particles would be everywhere too. Like in Charlie's picture, showing that hsi particles could be shown in a balloon."	2
"Charlie's claim is that the gas particles in a box spread out evenly everywhere. The teacher told him that when you blow air into a balloon, the balloon gets bigger in all directions. Charlie's claim is the same thing, in a box."	2
"This evidence shows that because the balloon expands in all directions. This would support Charlieå«s claim because it also shows that the air particles would move in all directions, making them look scattered."	2
"This evidence,""When you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions,"" could be used to support Charlie's claim, because giving the gas particles in the box time to separate and spread out throughout the box and go out in all directions, like how when you blow air into a balloon, it grows larger in all directions. Gas particles must spread out for the expansion of the balloon."	2
"This piece of evidence can be used to support Charlie's claim because he states that ""When you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions."" This shows that the particles are spread out evenly because it is growing in all directions."	1
Air particles move around really fast which cause the balloon to get bigger. This what is shown in Charlie's image.	0
"This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim because as you blow into the balloon, you are blowing a steady stream of air but as the air goes in, the particles spread to cause the balloon to grow bigger."	1
"Since you blow air into a balloon and the balloon expands, all the gas particles are evenly spreading throughout the space, therefore this also happens in my scenario so my claim is right."	2
That the box is enlarging.	0
This explains that Charlies diagram is also right.	0
This evidence might support Charlie's claim because the gas particles spread out when a balloon grows bigger.	1
"He could say that he is correct because when you blow air in a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions."	0
"Like in a balloon, the particles move in all directions."	2
like ballon the suger goes to all dirctions.	0
because the particles are everywhere	0
since the balloon is stretchy when you blow in air molecules the molecules bounce around in the balloon and make it larger and bigger	1
"Charlie could use this as evidence to support his claim because he could write ""Like in a balloon the air moves, or the particles spread around and so they probably do that in everything."""	2
"Charlie thinks that all the gas particles will be scattered all over the place because when you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all different directions."	1
When you blow into a balloon every gas particle go everywhere	1
The air blown into the balloon will grow bigger in all directions. It shows that the air particle was spreading inside the balloon. So the air is the similar to the gas particles so it supports Charlieå«s claim.	2
The evidence the teacher told Charlie could support Charlie's claim because Charlie drew gas particles that float around. The teacher told Charlie that air in a balloon could grow bigger in all directions.	1
It could help him to give examples in his evidence.	1
This evidence supports Charlie's claim because the particles when they blow in something they move around.	0
"If a balloon grows bigger in all directions, that can maybe support Charlie's claim."	0
The teacher is right because when you blow air the particles move they donå«t stay in one place only.	0
So that the bigger it gets more the particles separate.	0
This evidence supports the claim that gas particles spread out when traped in a box because the air in the balloon also spreads out to make the balloon expand.	2
Charlie's desgin is a moving in a air ballon	0
He could use this to support his claim because helium or carbon dioxide is a type of gas so when you blow up a balloon which at first has no gas in it when you blow it up it expands in all directions so therefore his claim would be right because his claim was that the particles would spread out in all directions.	1
charlie thinks that now that he know some air particles go in every direction he thinks his answer is correct.	0
The gas particles go around and donå«t stay all in one place	0
"This evidence could support Charlie's claim because as time goes on, the air starts to spread in different directions like how air in a balloon does."	2
That the particles do spread out in a balloon in all directions.	1
This evidence could be used to support Charlie‰Ûªs claim because the particle might fill up a balloon.	0
The gas particals might move around like a balloon's would.	0
"The gas spreads apart, making the balloon bigger, until it has too much gas, then it pops."	1
That you blow air then the air particles move up and around.	0
It could support his claim because it could be a diagram of how the gas particles move inside a balloon.	0
"When you blow a balloon, carbon dioxide gets into the balloon, which makes it grow in all directions. It is very easy to do and you just need a little bit of effort to do it."	0
"If the particles were in a balloon and I blew into it, then the particles would go everywhere to make the balloon grow bigger."	1
his did have more detail cause the gas moves the particales around	0
Charlie is thinking about when you blow a balloon the balloon doesn't just get blown up on 1 side actually it would blow up on all of the sides	0
"When you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions. This box also has gas particles and they will go everywhere like the balloon."	2
This evidence could be used because Charlie's drawing shows the gas particles moving in all directions and not being compact.	0
"This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim because the gas particles moved in all directions, like a balloon."	2
This helps Charlie`s claim because it gives evidence that particles spread out in some cases	0
That air goes in all directions.	0
"If you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions than Charlie can use this information to support his claim by saying that when you blow air to in the balloon, heat is being transferred and is causing the gas particles to move all over the place."	1
"This evidence would support CharlieÝ claim because Charlie thinks that the particles in a box spread around, and the teacher told him that in a balloon, the particles are spread around."	1
This can be used to support Charlies claim because he said the gas particles move everywhere just like they do in a ballon.	2
If particles float apart in a balloon maybe they do it in other places to.	1
"Air is made of particles, and the air in the balloon spreads, so these particles will also spread."	2
"Maybe he rode a hot air balloon and he knows that the gas particles spread out inside. Also, because the gas particles move in all sorts of directions."	1
The particles in a balloon spread when blown into.	1
"This evidence might be used to help Charlie's claim because when air is blown into a balloon, the pressure is greater than when it didn't have air in it."	0
This evidence supports Charlie's claim because Charlie drew all the particles spreading apart in the box.	0
This evidence can be used to support Charlie's claim by showing that the particles can go in all directions and expand its shape like a balloon being blown up.	2
This can be used for a balloon model of particle movement.	0
The air in his diagram takes up more space	0
"This evidence could be used to support Charlie‰Ûªs claim because when you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions. In his drawing, it shows the gas particles all around the box, just like balloon particles when blown into."	2
"This evidence may support Charlie's claim because if the balloon expands in all directions, it means the particles are in a position similar to his model."	0
"The teacher's evidence supports Charlie's claim, because in a balloon air goes in all directions, which is what Charlie drew in the diagram."	1
"when it is a balloon, it grows into a bigger directions"	0
because he is saying that the particles go everywhere	0
