review	label
Because his dots are spread out in every direction.	0
it can go in all directions	0
Because the gas in a balloon is expanding just like charlie's drawing	2
well air is a gas	0
Since the teacher also told Charlie that once you blow into a balloon it could go into all types of directions.	0
He thinks that the particles will spread out and if it happens with balloons it should happen with this too.	2
His particles spread out more instead of staying impact like Sam's.	0
"the particles spread out, making the balloon bigger"	1
Because of the gas inside the balloon goes everywhere	1
It shows that the particles go everywhere and his dots are everywhere.	0
The particals spread out and get bigger when they spread out and expands.	0
"This supports his claim because the air in the balloon spreads out to make the balloon bigger, like his diagram."	2
gas expands	0
Because there is no liquid to make the gas rise so it can bounce around.	0
He could also use this as an example and he could tell people how the example and gas in a room are close to the same thing.	0
There is partials all over the balloon so when you blow into it it gets bigger in all directions and his particals on his notebook are everywhere.	1
"This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim, because he thinks that gas particles float around, and the teacher tells him that when you blow up a balloon, the gas will go in different directions, so he could use that in an argument."	1
the gas in the balloon is spreading out	1
if the balloon grows bigger in all directions as you put more gas into it then the gas in his box must spread out	1
The water will expand with air	0
When blowing a air balloon it go's every way to become bigger because it's trapped in one space.	0
"The gas particles spread out, making the ballon expand."	1
The gas is expanding in all directions and not just going to the top.	0
that means the gas from your mouth will act like that.	0
Charlie is not correct because gas bubbles do not stay stationary they move around and they will float to the top	0
This supports charleis findings because it shows all the gas particles in all directions	0
"Charlie could say that after each minute the particles in the balloon spread out, so the gas particles do also."	2
"Charlie claimed that the gas would separate out. This is similar to how a balloon works. There is a fact (the air in the balloon spreads out) that supports his evidence, because we know this fact is true."	1
This shows how gas particles want to spread out and get as far away from each other as possible.	0
"Similar to Sam, Charlie will take this information and use it as an example of when gas particles spread out."	0
The particles are all spreading out and blowing up the balloon in all the different directions.	1
This evidence supports Charlie's claim because air is a type of gas-particle and if it is blown into a balloon it will expand on all directions which is what Charlie claimed. Charlie claimed that the gas particles will be dispersed in all directions.	1
"Charlies claim is that the particles spread out, ""When you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions"" is an example of particles spreading out into multiple directions."	2
"This could help Charlies claim because he believe that the gas particles will scatter in every direction, the balloon particles go in different directions; this would support his claim."	1
"Charlie could use this to support Charlie's claim. As an example, Charlie could use this information to justify Charlie's claim."	0
Charlie's claim is that gas/air evenly disperses and that claim is represented in his illustration. If a balloon grows in all directions when the air is added into it then the air within the balloon is constantly evenly in the space of the balloon. The balloon is an example of his claim.	2
"This evidence can support Charlie's claim because the when you blow air into the balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions which mean that the gas particles in the balloon move into all directions as you can see in Charlies' drawing."	2
This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim because gas expands a balloon in all directions which means that the gas particles could spread out in all directions.	1
"This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim because the balloon expands on all sides when you blow into it, just like Charlie's drawing of the air particles"	2
"Because balloons trap air and grow in all directions. Charlie isn't providing the most sufficient claim either, but it's good they can both think of examples."	0
"Charlie's prediction was that the gas particles 

XXX"	0
"The evidence that when the air is blown into a balloon, it swells is useful to Charlie's claim because his particles spread out evenly across the box"	1
"Charlie used this evidence to support this question because he knew that the air that was blown into a balloon spreads evenly, and therefore, so would the gas within the box."	2
"since the balloon inflates in all directions, the air flows freely in those, so why cant the particles float freely in the box?"	2
it supports Charlie's claim because it is an example of gas moving in all directions	0
Charlie could think that gas spreads everywhere.	0
It doesn' t support Charlie's claim as much because you are not blowing into the box. But now you know that there are cases where that happens	0
"When you blow ""gas"" into an balloon it grows bigger in all directions, that would mean that the gas particles are spreading out."	1
"The evidence supports Charlie's claim because he said that the gas expanded. Like in a balloon, the gas in his box could expand and go in all different directions after one minute."	2
He is thinking that in a ballon when you but air in it expands in all directions so should the air in the box	2
"Since the gas molecules spread out to every corner of the balloon, maybe the gas molecules do the same when they are not in the balloon."	2
"When a balloon is being blown into it inflates in every direction so, so would gas particles."	1
"It could suppot his claim because it is saying that the air, just like in a ballon, spreads out to all different sides and directions in the box, just like charlies drawing."	2
"Gas particles in a balloon move in all different directions, thats why the balloon moves out and up."	1
This could support Charlie's claim because the air would be spreading out in all directions just like how Charlie thinks the gas particles would.	0
"This evidence can mean that gas particles will move around everywhere when put into one space, because of the fact that when it is put into a balloon it does that. He could say that although a balloon is not the same thing as a box, it might not matter what type of space the gas in in, and it might always spread out everywhere."	1
Because a ballon separates with air inside of it the gas will also separate because there is air in the box.	2
"Gas particles are also like balloons. as the gas particles expand, so does the balloon."	1
The balloon is exactly what he's talking about so it helps him because it's evidence of his claim	0
because air goes into the balloon everywhere that's what makes it blow up and he shows that they are all around.	1
"The ballon evidence could show that when gas particles are blown into a ballon they go out in every direction, like in this picture. It would prove that the gas inflates in ever direction."	2
If in a balloon the gas makes the balloon grow in all directions then Charlie's claim is supported because he thinks that the gas will rise everywhere.	2
It goes all over the place which is what he showcased.	0
"Because Charlie thinks that gas particles go in all directions like when you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions."	2
Because balloons spread out when you blow into them and those are particles so why can't the box also be like that.	2
the balloon is holding air that is spreading out just like in Charlie's drawing	2
Charlie's diagram shows particles everywhere or " in all directions" as his teacher mentioned.	0
the balloon gets bigger when you blow air into it which means it stretches in all directions which means the air is cause pressure across the whole area of the ballon.	1
"He can make a diagram to show that when there is air going in, the balloon gets bigger, so he can make a drawing. He can also put a go-pro in the ballon and show that when air goes in, it gets bigger and it doesn't go up, like helium balloons."	0
"This evidence would support Charlie's claim, because the Co2 that you blow into a balloon spreads out because it is the same weight, or a bit heavier than the air it is in, so it doesn't go up."	1
"This could help Charlie because he could claim if you blow helium gas into a balloon the balloon stretches and spreads out, therefore the gas particles must be the ones pushing the balloon out by spreading out,"	1
The air in a balloon spreads out to form an oval shape.	1
This could support Charlie's claim because if a balloon blows up it means that the gas is expanding outwards. In his drawing that is what is being shown.	2
Air is pushing on the sides of the balloon which is expanding the balloon.	1
This could help Charlie's claim by saying gas will expand in every way no matter what substance it is in.	0
This could support his claim because Charlie said that all the particles would separate and that's what happens with balloons	2
The balloon gets bigger everywhere because the air goes everywhere so the gas particles could go everywhere if the air goes everywhere.	2
"When thinking about how the particles look Charlie probably thought that when there is air somewhere, it would spread out in all directions, like a ballon. Another example is the oxygen all around us. It does not clump up in one place in the sky."	2
This supports Charlie's claim because it's saying that air moves in all directions when you're blowing a balloon if the air was in a ballon then Charlie's claim would be correct.	1
It could help Charlie's claim because in his graph his particles are everywhere	0
This evidence could support Charlie's claim because it shows how Charlie's teacher just told him that gas can disperse in some cases.	0
"When gas particles are placed in a balloon, they spread out and push on the side of the balloon in all directions, not just up."	1
The gas is spreading.	0
The gas is spreading out in the balloon. That is what is happening in the drawing.	2
"Because when you blow air into a balloon and it grows in all directions, then the particles would also grow in all directions when contained in a box."	2
"Charlie is saying that the gas particles spread out through the glass. The teacher is saying that blowing air into a balloon makes it bigger. The air particles are spread out through the balloon. (which doesn't relate to water, because you are not blowing air into it)"	1
This can be used as evidence for Charlie's claim because it is saying that the balloon grows bigger in all directions and that matches Charlie's drawing.	0
This can be used to support his claim because his said that they all spread out. In a balloon they do the same and this can connect is to real life more.	1
This could be used to support Charlies claim because the gas molecules are spread out just like it is in the picture.	0
"Charlie's claim was that the gas particles would start from one spot and spread through all directions of the box, like when you blow up a balloon, the gas particles don't go in one direction, they go in multiple."	2
"If the balloon grows bigger in all directions, Charlie is showing how all the air is spread out"	1
This evidence supports Charlie's claim because when you put air into a balloon it goes into different directions. This is what Charlie wrote down in his notebook.	2
He is saying that when you blow into a balloon the air fills up the whole ballon and spreads throughout the inside of the ballon. It doesn't just float to the top.	1
"Charlie could argue that if the air particles didn't spread out, than the balloon would only grow bigger in one direction when air was blown into it."	1
Charlie thinks that when gas enters a balloon the gas spreads out evenly created the balloons shape and he thinks the same will happen to the gas particles when in a box.	2
"If the particles are the air particles in the balloon, then if the balloon air spreads out, then the particles spread as well."	2
"Charlie's gas particles spread out in all directions, just like a balloon does. If gas particles only rose, then balloons would be long and skinny instead of wide."	2
Charlie could be right because you are blowing carbon dioxide into the balloon which is a gas and the balloon expand in many different ways.	0
that when you blow a bolloon this is right.	0
"If it gets bigger in all directions, it's spread out across all directions."	0
This helps Charlie's claim because he is explaining his theory and giving some personal experience why he thinks that.	0
"it would help because in a way, it's all spreading out inside the box, like it is in the balloon."	0
In a balloon the particles flout midair.	0
The evidence could be used to support charlies claim by saying that gas particles spilt up when you blow a ballon cause the gas particles inside it are not togheter wich blows up the ballon.	1
that the gas expanded	0
"This evidence supports Charlie's claim because if the balloon grows bigger and expands in all directions, the air must be expanding too."	1
because his gas particles go in all directions.	0
the teachers evidence supports charlie's claim because the teacher is using an example to support the claim	0
the bubbles are in the middle	0
the dots sped out when a balloon grows	0
"This says that gas particles spread apart in the air, which supports Charlie's claim because the depiction of his claim was that the gas particles would spread apart in the box."	0
the spreading out makes the balloon spread out and as the teacher said grows bigger	1
This could be used to support Charlie's claim because it's evidence that the particles move around. When air is blown inside the balloon gets pushed by the particles and increases it's size.	1
What the teacher told Charlie was that when air is blown into a balloon it grows bigger and bigger and this is because the gas particals have to flout in every direction in order to make the balloon grow and so to do that the gas particals have to be everywhere and spread out and that is what Charlie's claim is.	2
"The picture charlie drew is gas particles spreading in all directions and the teacher said when you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions."	1
The air makes the balloon bigger and the particles become more spaced out	1
"The air in a balloon spreads out just like in Charlie's diagram.

."	2
That a balloon grow bigger because the gas particles goes every diction	1
The air pushes the balloon out and isn't just going in one direction. If it was just going up it would be more of a rod shape.	1
"This supports Charlie's claim because when you blow are into a balloon it grows in all directions so, the gas would be spread out rather than in one location of the balloon"	1
"The air in a balloon depending on how much air you put into it, expands into a big sphere which is even."	1
"Charlie drew the chemicals that are always moving, and they are not separated 

from each other."	0
When blowing into a balloon the air is forced into an expandable weak substance and is trying to make more room so the gas could force its way out.	0
"Charlie's claim is that particles would float anywhere in every direction. å¬When you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions,"" supports Charlie's claim because what Charlie drew is the same action as what the teacher told him."	2
"because it said the balloon grow bigger in all directions, that mean the air goes at all direction too, and at all place."	1
This proves that gas spreads out evenly in all directions.	0
when you blow up the balloon your adding air to the balloon which makes the particles move differently with the additional air	0
The gas bubbles stay in the middle because the air is pushing them in from all sides.	0
"Since blowing air into a balloon expands in all directions, gas particles in a box must expand as well."	2
it expands	0
"Since the air put in the balloon is scattered in all directions, the glass particles should also be scattered in all directions."	2
The particles can be going all over the place and be how like Charlie had drew in his picture that is inside his notebook.	0
He is saying that the gas in a balloon spreads around everywhere.	1
the sugar is not going to spread out in the soda if you open the soda all the cool gas comes out	0
the evidence could support charlie's claim by the teacher also telling him that when you blow the air balloon the balloon grows bigger.	0
When you blow air into the balloon it spreads out and expands the balloon making it bigger and bigger until there is no more room to expand and just pops	1
The gas paticles are all over the place.	0
"This might support Charlie's claim, as this is saying that the particles will go in each directions, giving air to all parts of the balloon, and Charlie says the particles will spread evenly apart in all directions, the evidence and Charlie's opinion match."	2
"That means that the air in the balloon would spread out, just like the particles in Charlie's claim."	2
This follows Charlieå«s claim because the teacher stated how the balloon gets bigger when you blow air into it which means that the gas particles are spreading	1
Charlie made the assumption that the gas particles would spread apart since they do that same when blowing up a balloon.	2
The evidence can be used to supports Charlie's claim because the gas spreads all over the place in both the balloon and the box	2
I think that this evidence supports my claim because the gas particles had moved around in the bubble and that means that the gas particles have spread out	0
"The gas particles do spread out in a balloon when its being blown in to. And if it is compared to the drawing he drew, he would have a good piece of evidence."	2
"Gas is air and its all spread out. When the air is going into the balloon, it grows bigger and the gas particles are jumping everywhere. Gas fills up the container."	1
the gas in the balloons spreed so the gas in the box will too	2
so when you blow into a balloon it gets bigger and when you blow into bubble gum it gets bigger so all the particles are going around to create more space so it can get bigger.	1
"The air inside the balloon does not only go up, it goes all around the balloon evenly."	1
it grows in all directions	0
that the gas wants to go in the air	0
more air equal more space.	0
the balloon is rubber and can expand a lot so the gas in a balloon move around the balloon.	1
If the balloon grows bigger than the particles have more space to spread and it will then look like his drawing.	1
"When you blow a balloon the gas particles go in different directions, not staying together, making Charlie's explanation true."	1
"Once you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger and bigger. Therefore, once you leave the box alone in one minute, the particles must go all over the place just like the balloon."	2
they have motion they can go where ever	0
when there is this one type of gas then yes it will be moving around	0
"When you blow into a balloon, the air makes the balloon bigger and bigger based on how much air you blow into it. the air then keeps the balloon big when you tie up the balloon. The same thing goes for the gas particals in the box"	0
"when the balloon goes bigger, the gas would spread out to make the balloon big"	1
"In a way there both the same because the particles don't just rise up,they go in every direction the particles spread out that why when u blow into a balloon it gets bigger because the particles spread out"	2
because all the bubbles of the soda can fill into the balloon and make the balloon bigger	0
because it will settle and will desolve	0
Because Charlie says the particles go in random places like how it would if you blow up a balloon.	2
this is not a solid block of beans will report my memes are seamed dead	0
the particles go all around inside the balloon	0
"This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim because his drawing claims that the gas particles go in all directions, just as the balloon grows bigger in all directions."	2
because the gas is everywhere.	0
Because those particles can go and be free because they have more space than a soda can.	0
The gas particles in the balloon after blowing it pushes the balloon outwards making it bigger.	0
The evidence could be used to support Charlies claim because the picture of the gas in the box shows all the gas that is spreed around the box	0
"This evidence can be used to support Charlie's claim by him showing that the particles are stretched out just like if someone were blowing a balloon, the balloon would expand as well."	2
"Charlie says that gas particles spread out, in all directions. If a balloon expands out in all directions, it supports Charlie's claim (because that would mean the air goes in all directions, like Charlie says)."	2
"When air is blown, it is hot or cold, that could be what affects the particles."	0
because his are scattered.	0
He saying that the particles when inside they move around to blow up the balloon.	1
This helps support his claim because it says that gas particles move all around and don't just apply to one spot.	0
If you blow air into a balloon then the particles become spaced out so that must be the same with gas particles in a box.	2
The hydrogen and oxygen molecules are still close so they didn't rise.	0
That when you blow the balloon the air will move freely like blow air at your hand to harm you up the air goes freely	0
"This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim because when you blow into a balloon, the gas particles spread out and make the balloon expand in different directions."	1
Saying it expands more when it is more spread out.	0
"The teacher states that‰ÛÏWhen you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions.‰Û which eventually mean the gas particles will spread all through the balloon."	1
"This supports Charlie's claim because if you blow up a balloon it gets bigger and bigger and once you tie it you can notice on every part or side of the balloon, it got bigger."	0
"This evidence supports Charlie's claim because Charlie draw the gas particles moving in every direction and when you blow up a balloon, the gas molecules spread as it expands."	2
when the gas is inside it gets bigger every were and it soon escapes	0
Because they are all split up and they are in all directions	0
"This evidence can be used to support Charlie's claim because to make the balloon expand, the gas must spread out to make the balloon bigger."	1
This supports Charlie's claim because the gases inside the balloon expands the balloon.	1
The bubble is confined in an balloon. The bubble will form the balloon into a shape and is spread throughout.	0
"The gas particles in the balloon support Charlie's claim, because the particles move slowly and start to slowly split, meaning less energy is in the particles."	1
"This evidence could support Charlies claim because it shows that in certain conditions gas particles spread out enlarging the item
."	0
this claim also makes sense but in the picture it seems that there aren't enough particles or gas bubbles to fill up the whole box therefore this claim is irrelevant for Charlie's claim.	0
Charlies evidence does support his claim and his evidence is true because the gas particles inside of the balloon can blow up in many different ways.	1
i think that this helps charlies claim by showing that gas can expand and go spread out	0
The same thing he just imagine that he is blowing to a balloon.	0
"This could be used to support his claim because gas particles do spread out and fill up space. so when you blow air into a balloon, that's why it gets bigger."	1
"The balloon is growing bigger because the gas particles are all spreading out, which is similar to what Sam drew in his notebook."	2
"This evidence might be used to support Charlie's claim because now he knows that if gas particles do actually look like how he drew them, he has evidence and that is that ""When you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions."""	1
"This evidence can support Charlie's claim because in his claim he drew that the gas particles spread out. so that fact that the teacher said ""when you blow air in a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions' can totally explain why he thought what he thought.
.."	1
Gas tends to spread out when exposed to air. Like when you blow into a balloon. you are blowing air into it and all of the gas particles in it are just going to spread out.	1
This evidence would be used to support Charlie's claim because if you add more gas particles the particles would be everywhere.	0
This evidence can be used to support his claim because he can demonstrate it and the balloon won't just grow bigger on one side.	0
"Once you blow air into a balloon the air doesn't just stay in one spot it moves around so that the balloon can get bigger and bigger,so charlie's claim was that the gas particles move around."	1
The evidence can support Charlie's claim because the evidence shows that the gas particles are spread out exactly like Charlie's claim	0
This evidence could be used to support charlies claim because the particles inside a balloon are moving around everywhere which causes the balloon to inflate.	1
that the air has spread throughout the whole entire area that was given	0
"The balloon is just like the gas particles, it gets mixed around"	0
Charlie could use this because when you blow air into a balloon it expands all directions and what his drawing is saying that the air particles are going everywhere or they are everywhere.	1
when its a balloon it does grow bigger and that is a really good support.	0
The gas particles will move all around everywhere so that thing will get bigger.	0
"Out of all the states of matter like solid, liquid and gaseous, this is gaseous. Think of the gaseous state like a kid very energetic among the crowd of people. Gases have the most heat so they have the most energy like a hot air balloon it is able to rise up because of the particles moving fast. If you look at gas it is spread out as they are moving in different directions"	1
That the gas can go any where that is why it will be in different directions	0
"They expand and they spread out away from each other just like when you blow a balloon, it's small and mushed up but when you blow, it expands and gets bigger"	1
This evidence used to supports Charlie's claim because the balloon is filled with air particle.	0
He thinks that when the air rises it will go in different directions like a balloon.	1
"The gas takes up space, inflating the balloon."	1
This evidence can be used because there are different directions that the air goes when you blow into a balloon.	1
The gas goes everywhere when you blow up a balloon	1
Charlie thinks that since you blow air into a balloon it goes bigger in every direction but I think that it doesn't really work like that.	0
"Since balloon grows bigger in all direction , it shows us that gas spreads in all direction, which will support his statement."	1
the particles in the balloon spread out equally	1
The particles in a ballon are an example of Charlie's claim.	0
"When a balloon is blown, it is added more air or gas into it which means its expanding because of the gas or air."	1
when you blow a balloon the air goes to all equal sides for the air so the balloon is equally sided with the oxygen given inside the balloon.	1
The balloon get bigger on all sides because the gas spreads into all directions.	1
The gas goes all over until the balloon is fully blown	1
"Charlie could argue that if a balloon grows bigger in all directions, the gas particles are spreading out evenly, just like his picture."	2
"Thus evidence can support Charlie's claim as when air is blown into the balloon, the gas particles move out in all directions."	1
I think that this information can be used to support Charlie's claim because the air pushes the balloon in all directions causing the balloon to expand all around. Charlie stated that the particles spread out which would cause the same thing.	2
"This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim by arguing that if the molecules move in all directions, then they would go in all directions."	0
"This supports Charlie's claim because Charlie says the the air is spread out (in all directions), just like the teacher's balloon example."	2
"Charlie claims that the gas particles would try to fill up as much space as possible. When the balloon is blown up, the gas or air particles try to fill up as much of the space of the balloon as possible filling the balloon up."	0
"This evidence can be used to support Charlie's claim, since the pressure is changed when you blow air into the balloon, making the particles spread out from one another."	1
"Charlie could use the example of how blowing air into a balloon causes the gas to spread in all directions, therefore leading the balloon to grow bigger in all directions, not just at the top, to support his claim that gas particles will spread out."	1
The gas particles when blown in a balloon must spread out and disperse to result in the balloon expanding.	1
This evidence could be used to support Sam's claim. This is because he could assume that the gas in the space would act like the gas in a balloon and expand.	2
"This evidence could be used like this:
When air is blown into a balloon, the air particles are spread out into the ball in all directions which inflates the balloon and makes it grow. This means that whenever particles are placed into a container, the particles will disperse to fit the need of the container. Therefore in my picture, the particles are dispersed after one minute."	0
This evidence helps because it is saying that the gas is spreading out and expanding the balloon and the drawing also looks the air particles are expanding in different directions	2
"This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim because, when the particles stay in the box they spread because they have more room."	0
"This evidence can be used to support Charlie's claim because when you blow into the balloon it will grow from all sides, so it is not distorted. This means that the particles will spread out over time."	1
"This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim, because it's similar to what he stated. Having an example could help to explain why he believes gas will behave a certain way."	0
"This evidence can be used to support Charlie's claim because the teacher said that if you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions which means that the gas particles have to be spread out (which is similar to the drawing in Charlie's claim)."	2
"The air blown into balloons is gas (air is gas), and the air causes the balloon to become bigger. The balloon expands in all directions, so Charlie is saying that the gas is going in all directions."	1
"When you hold a balloon, it is floppy, and has no shape. But if you are to blow air (gas) into it, it will expand in all directions. This is because gas particles shoot in different directions, constantly bouncing off one another."	1
This shows that if it did the opposite it would look as if you put a rock into the balloon.	0
"Air is a type of gas, and when it is used, it can spread anywhere."	0
"This could support his claim because if the gas in balloons spread out to expand the balloon, then the gas particles in the box will too."	2
Charlies claim is that gas travels everywhere so when you blow a balloon all the gas goes everywhere too.	2
I believe that this information can be used to support Charlie's statement because the air spreads out in all directions causing the balloon to spread out.	1
"The gas particles in the original drawing show them tightly packed together at the bottom of the box. In Charlie's drawing, he drew the gas particles spread out, and all over the box, similar to blowing up a balloon. Blowing air into a balloon causes the balloon to get bigger, just like how Charlie depicted it. The originally close particles spread out and covered a larger expanse of area, increasing in size just like a balloon when air is continually blown into it."	2
"Charlies claim was that overtime the gas particles will spread apart, like a balloon it gets bigger which means the particles need to spread out."	2
"This could be used to support Charlie's claim because gasses are always moving in random directions, so gasses typically would not stay in a small area for very long."	0
"This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim because he drew the gas particles expanding and going out in all directions, just like how when you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions."	2
"Charlie can use this evidence to support his claim by stating that the gases one blows in a balloon makes it bigger, then gas must expand outward evenly."	1
in charles statement about the ballon he stated that the particles will be evenly spaced out and it is here	1
"Charlie's claim is that the particles spread out in all directions, like how the balloon gets bigger. The particles are similar to the air spreading out."	2
"Because the balloon is filled up entirely, in all areas, by the gas/air, it means the gas particles must fill up an entire closed object, like the balloon."	2
"When you blow the air into a balloon, the gas particles spread out in every direction. The same thing will happen when you put these gas particles in a box; they will spread out."	2
"This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim because all the air particles go in all directions, like Sam's scattered particle drawing."	0
Since the air in a balloon spreads out the gas in a box should also spread out because they're both gas	2
This evidence shows that when air or gas is inside something is spreads out in all directions just like it should in the box.	0
"Charlie could use this to support his claim because it has the same idea as Charlie's claim. Charlie's image implies that he thinks the gas molecules will spread out, similarly to when you blow into a balloon and the balloon grows bigger in all directions."	2
"This could be used to help support Charlie's claim because he draws the particles expanding outwards in the box, similar to air in a balloon."	2
"Charlie says that the gas particles will spread out over time within the container. The teacher states that ‰ÛÏWhen you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions.‰Û The gas is expanding the growing in all directions just like how the gas is expanding in the container."	2
"The evidence that Charlie gave could be used to support his claim. For example, when you blow us a balloon, the balloon expands in all different directions. And the way for that to happen is for the air inside to be spread out, even. Therefore, after one minute, the gas particles would be spread out."	2
"This could be used as evidence by saying that when you blow up a balloon, the it expands in all directions, so the gas must also expand in all directions."	2
"Charlie's claim is that the particles will spread apart. The teacher tells Charlie that the balloon becomes bigger as you blow more air into it. As more gas particles enter the balloon, the balloon will grow bigger as the particles spread apart."	1
The evidence can support Charlie because it can give him an example to explain his claim.	0
"Since the air (gas bubbles) in the balloon expands in all direction and the bubbles on charlie's sheet did the same, you could argue that he's right."	2
"This can be used to support Charlie's claim because in his drawing, the molecules are separating."	0
"The molecules are spreading out equally, therefore pushing the balloon sides out in all directions"	1
This could be used to support Charlie's claim because he predicted that the gas particles would spread in all directions and its a fact that air particles spread in all different directions in a balloon.	1
The teacher uses Charlie's picture to make a true statement that corresponds with his picture.	0
"This could support Charlie's claim, because the particles are spread all around the area."	0
"When the teacher said when you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions, Charlie inferred that all gas bubbles float in all directions."	1
"This evidence is used to support Charlies claim, because since his claim was that gas spreads throughout the box, then that means since the spreads all throughout the balloon to help it expand, then it must spread throughout the container to."	2
Charlie stated the gas particles will evenly space out over time. The teacher said that the air expands in all directions. This can help prove Charlie's hypothesis because the air is expanding everywhere and not at the top.	2
"This evidence can't be used to support Charlie's claim, sorry Charlie."	0
if a balloon gets blown up with hellium it flout and get bigger but how would the particles that have gas in them spread out?	1
that the particles are moving around in that space that is getting bigger and bigger	0
"When you blow air into a balloon, the air particles scatters. Charlie could support his claim using this information."	1
"When you blow air into a balloon, the air particles take the shape of the balloon and spread out causing the balloon to expand."	1
the gases are expanding.	0
she is saying the air spears out	0
"The gas particles are like the balloon, spreading out in all directions."	2
"This can support Charlie's claim because he stated that the gas particles fill up their contained space, and his teacher had just given him and example of how gas particles in a balloon do that very thing."	0
"because when you blow up a balloon, you are blowing gas into it and it expands in all directions.if the gas only went in one direction, the balloon will onlyexpand in that one direction."	1
"Since charlies claim is gas will spead all around the box this is the same as When you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions"	2
The more gas particles that are in the balloon the more the balloon stretches.	0
This is also true when you breath oxygen into the balloon.	0
"The air particles are all spread out . When you blow into a balloon, it expands. The particles are evenly spaced so when they go into the balloon, it pushes apart."	1
charlie is wrong	0
"This evidence could support Charlie's claim because when you blow air into a balloon, the air grows bigger in all directions of the balloon. Same could happen to Charlies idea that all the particles will go in all the directions of the box since air is a particle."	2
"This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim because the air in the balloon is taking up all the available space inside of the balloon, similar to how the gas particles take up the space in the box."	2
"The evidence the teacher told Charlie supports his claim because he said how the gas particles scatter around the box and not all go at the same place and to the same direction, just like a balloon."	2
"As you begin to blow air into a balloon in it grows up and at different angles, expanding the balloon.The air fills the balloon and is in all parts of the balloon."	1
Both examples are gas particles so they have a similarity which charlie can use as evidence	0
"This could be used as evidence to support Charlie's claim by showing and explaning that when air is added to the balloon, the gas bubble goes everywhere, which makes the balloon expand."	1
In Charlie's picture he drew that the gas starts moving and when you blow air into a balloon it starts to increase in size because of the particles that are moving inside.	0
"This evidence suprrot Charile by the praticles move in all direction, like a balloon growing bigger"	2
"This could support charlies evidence because in his claim the gas particles seperate, and in a balloon the gas seperates and makes the balloon bigger."	1
Charlies claim is that gas particles will scatter in one minute.	0
scince the particals are all sread out the balloon grows	1
"When the balloon grows bigger, it grows in different directions, in Charlie's picture, the gas particles are in every direction, spread out."	1
baloons particle spread out very far	1
"This supports Charlie's evidence because the teacher is proving that in balloons, the gas particles spread out in all directions like in Charlie's notebook."	2
"Charlie claims that the gas floats around and the teacher said that when you blow in a balloon, the balloon expands in all directions which is what Charlie drew in his notebook."	2
This evidence could be used to support his claim because the pas particles in the balloon spread and grows bugger in all directions. This is similar to what Charlie showed in his diagram.	2
"This can support his claim because he drew his particles spread out and going in different directions, like a balloon."	2
This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim because Charlie drew that after one minute gas molecules float everywhere.	0
This supports Charlies claim because when you blow air into the balloon all the particles are distributed across the area inside the balloon.	1
As i said before evidence and claim and pictures.	0
"This evidence could support Charlie's claim because his picture shows particles spread out. So if a balloon is expanding in all directions, the particles would spread out, looking like this."	1
"The teacher is saying that the gas particles cover every inch to inflate the area, as depicted in Charlie's picture."	0
This proves that the gas particles will scatter	0
"because the air you exhale into a balloon is a gas, and like the air in the balloon this gas could go in all directions and try to disperse also"	2
"This supports Charlie's claim, because it relates to his drawing. Since it states the balloon goes in all directions, it matches the picture he drew about gas particles."	0
"He could write: When you blow up a balloon, the air particles spread and make the balloon bigger"	1
because it shows that its an example of how the particles spread out.	0
the air particles are spreading to fill the balloon.	1
Since Charlie believes that gas bubbles float everywhere his evidence can be once you blow air into a ballon the balloon grows bigger because the gas bubbles.	1
it shows that he was technically right in some way	0
That when you blow up a balloon the air does not just go to the top it fills up the whole space of the balloon.	1
it supports the claim because the gas particles are scattered everywhere	0
"Charlie, can use this to support his claim by adding on to his claim, like, My claim is that the gas particles fill in the spaces of the box, and an example of this is ‰ÛÏWhen you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions.‰Û."	2
because gas is all over the place.	0
"This evidence supports his claim because when you blow into a balloon, the Carbon spreads out to fill up the space in the balloon, showing that Charlie's claim about the gas spreading out in the box is true."	2
"When we blow balloon, it grows bigger in all directions."	0
because it shows that it has to spread in order to work	0
This will help Charlie because Cjarlie states that gas spreads out and that is what the teavher said.	0
That could help support Charlie's claim because when you blow air into a blown you blow gas particles into the balloon just like the air particles are in the box Charlie drawled.	0
"The particles fill the entire balloon, not just one section of it after being blown into. Just like how particles will try to fill up as much space as possible when contained."	1
When a balloon is blown up the air expands so the air tries to expand in the box.	1
This evidence shows that when there are so many particles i n one space they start to elevate and expand through the place they have been kept in.	0
blowing the balloon spreads out the particles	1
"Because he said gas spreads and because it expands in all directions, the gas travels in all directions"	0
"Because a balloon expands more and more as you blow in it, it could be that the gas particles spread more apart to expand the balloon."	1
"Since in a balloon for it to be able to grow it need air in side,which is particle.Meaning the balloon needs to be filled up with particles.Which mean it needs to be all over the balloon and spread apart."	1
"This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim because his claim was that the particles will scatter in all directions, so when the teacher said that in a balloon, it gets bigger in all directions, this means that if the box was filled with air, that the particles would scatter."	1
"How this evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim is that it says when you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows larger in all directions, just like how his gas particles also go out in all directions"	2
The evidence for this is the air must be all around the balloon not at a very top or a very end of the balloon. If the is at a very top of the balloon it will only grows bigger at the top of the balloon.	0
The air particles in a balloon bounce around and scatter in different directions.	1
the air would expand to fill up all the empty space in the balloon.	1
According to Charlie gas go in all diraction and fill up empty space and in Balloon when we blow it grow bigger as air go in all diraction	1
Air fills in space all around so it makes sense that Charlie's thinks gas will move around after 1 minute.	0
its saying that in the balloon the air is pushing out in all directions but there are also alot of particles in the middle area because that's how air works	1
He can also show an example by showing how when he blows up the balloon it expands all through out the balloon and not just to the top of the balloon	0
"Because Charlie claimed that the gas particles will move in all directions, and the evidence shows that gas particles move all directions in a balloon. This matches his claim and supports it as well."	2
"This evidence is an example of what Charlie said, and it is a fact"	0
This evidence can be used by giving a reference to others and help them better understand his picture claim.	0
because his gas molecules are spread all out witch explains how the balloon gets bigger in all parts	1
This could be used as evidence as well that when you do blow air into a balloon you could feel all the air expanding inside of the balloon.	1
"This will support Charlie's claim because if you blow air into a balloon all the air spreads to hold the balloon like that. And it shows the same in charlie's claim too , so the particles will spread more."	2
The air in the balloon was expanding.	1
"gas and liquid usually try to take the shape of whatver theyre in thus the ballon gets filled equally, and so maybe the box should too."	0
"This evidence could support Charlie's claimed as, in his drawing he had drawn his gas particle much more spread out and filling most of the box."	0
In charlie's picture he shows that gas will go in all directions and fill the whole container. The teacher is saying that the gas blown into the balloon everywhere in order to grow bigger. Which is very similar.	2
When u blow up a balloon it slowly begins to grow in all of the directions evenly that's because the particles in the air in side the balloon are spread out like the particles in the box in the pic	2
"He said the particles will be spread out, so now he too can use the teachers evidence to support his claim."	0
cuz the air or gas spreads out in the balloon cuz if it dont it will just fill with one side	1
Because Charlie's claim shows that gas particles spread out	0
a balloon does get bigger as you blow into it	0
"This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim because it says that the balloon will grow bigger in all directions, and in Charlieå«s picture it shows gas particles going in every direction"	1
"The teacher tells Charlie, ‰ÛÏWhen you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions.‰Û And that is what Charlie drew."	1
Charlie can say that oxygen atoms spread apart when in a open space.	0
"This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim because he drew gas particles everywhere in the box. Knowing that by blowing air into a balloon, it grows the balloon in all directions, he can make the connection that when air is in a box, the gas particles will go in all directions."	2
The gas that goes in the balloon is trying to show that the gas will go in different directions as do the particles.	1
"If blowing into a balloon will make it get larger in all directions, then particles must be moving in all directions too."	1
"The air particles try to fill the space in the balloon in all directions, causing it to grow bigger in all directions."	1
The gas spreads out in the balloon just like how it does in Charlies drawing.	2
"Charlie drew the particles are spread out, just like the gas particles are when filling up a balloon."	2
This evidence could be use to support Charlies claim because that it sounds like gas particle is the one taking up the space and making the balloon bigger.	1
The gas particles in the balloon fly to every empty space in the balloon	1
This can supports Charlie's claim because it shows how gas spreads out in all directions.	0
If it happens in a balloon why wouldnt it happen in a box?	0
Charlie's evidence is that a balloon gets bigger in all directions.	0
The gas will spread out in all directions filling up any empty space.	0
The particles to Charlie are like a balloon. The air goes to every point in the balloon. Therefor he thinks that the particles go everywhere.	1
because the baloon grows bigger	0
Charlie says the gas spreads. This is the same case with the balloon.	2
the gas particles are going in all directions.	0
"When blowing up the balloon, gas particles spread out and cover different areas so that the balloon can be blown up. He thinks the the gas particles would also spread out and cover different spaces."	1
"This piece of evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim because the air in a balloon makes it grow bigger in all directions, so air in a box would go in all directions too."	2
"Charlie's picture shows the gas particles spreading out. For a balloon to inflate, the gas particles would have to spread out, as shown in Charlie's picture."	2
"This evidence could prove that particles, not specifying gas particles, move in all sorts of directions. This could possibly prove that the gas particles float around."	0
that the air is scattered all over the place to direct the air	0
Gas spreads as much as possible.	0
Cause in a balloon the particles can start anywere	0
Charlie's claim shows how the particles move in all directions.	0
When you blow air into a ballon the gas particles go everywhere but when you release the gas from the ballon it goes up and flies back down.	1
Since the air you blow in it makes it go in all directions it could be the same for those particles.	0
Charlie said that the gas particles will float around in all different directions. The teacher's statement will help him because it matches his claim.	0
It supports it because it was proved with an experiment.	0
"A balloon expands as gas expands. They do not rise nor fall, but grow in size in all directions."	1
"The particles in Charlies box expanded and used up all the space in the box. This is what happens when you blow up a balloon, so his claim can also be true."	2
"This evidence can help support Charlie's claim because, his chart is like blowing air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions."	1
Charlie can use this infrmation the glaim when air is added to the particles they spread out just like a ballon.	1
The teacher is telling Charlie that when u blow a balloon it expands meaning the gas particles will spread out causing the balloon to expand. In Charlies drawing he said that the particles will expand filling the box.	1
This evidence can be used because its actually true unlike the other kid with the weird thinking the fart come out of the ears	0
all the air is spreading out and not going in one place	0
"This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim because he had drawn the particles rising but they are going different ways. Thus when you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all of the directions. Just like in Charlie's drawing the particles are going all ways and not just one."	2
Charlie's claim is the adding the gas would make the particles would go in different places in the box.	0
that gas will expan	0
This supports Charlie's claim because it is coming from a credible source that the gas in the balloon makes the balloon grow bigger in all directions.	1
"This can support Charlie's claim because his picture shows that gas particles spreading out more . Like the teacher said how the balloon grows bigger in all directions, Charlie's pictures shows the gas particles spreading out in all directions. helium is also a gas lighter than air."	2
the gass particals are all around spreading	0
"The teachers claim can be correct because if you blow into a balloon and the gas particles don't expand, the balloon won't expand either. I believe that gas particles move super fast and try to separate, compared to a solid where the matter is tightly packed together."	1
This supports Charlie's claim because he said that after one minute that the gas particles will be all over the place just like when you blow a balloon that the gas particles go all over the place that that is why the balloon grows bigger.	2
"The fact that when you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions can be helpful when supporting Charlie's claim because Charlie claims that after one minute of being in a box, all the gas particles spread themselves out among the whole box. The same thing happens when air is being blown into a balloon; the gas particles spread themselves out among the whole balloon as it continues to grow."	2
That when you let gas sit in a box it will scatter everywhere so it could spread	0
the balloon has particles that scatter when it blows up	1
The gas particles get more space and can move around more easily.	0
this evidence can help charlie because he thinks that all the particles with go everywhere and as what the teacher said when you blow a balloon all that air that you blow into it goes everywhere	1
CO2 carbon dioxide that you breath out into a balloon likes to travel outwards so the more you blow the more it will expand in size.Your giving the balloon some size the more you blow in it.	0
This could support Charlie's because it is showing that not all the gas goes in one direction it goes in multiple.	0
This evidence can help Charlie's claim because if a balloon gets bigger in all the sides then he might be right	0
"Charlie believes that gas particles inside a box will extend to all places inside a box after a minute. Balloons also do this when they are inflated, the gas inside of them extends outwards in order to make the balloon bigger."	2
This evidence can support Charlie's claim because when you blow into a balloon all the particles move around to make space for more.	1
because his goes in all directions	0
water isnt air	0
"This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim because like his diagram, which showcases the gas bubbles being all spread out in the box, the inside of the balloon would also look like that based on the teacher's statement."	2
"I think that evidence supports Charlie's claim because, in his picture all the particles are space out. And when you blow into a balloon and the air that grows inside the balloon goes different ways to fill in the space."	1
"The balloon gets bigger as gas is pumped in, so the gas in the container should do the same."	0
the ballo	0
"Charlie compared his diagram of gas particles to blowing air into a balloon, and how the balloon gets bigger."	0
"The evidence could support Charlie's claim because Charlie's claim shows the gas particles all spread out in all directions, and the evidence says that a balloon gets bigger because the air is in all directions."	1
Charlie might think: The air in the box will get bigger and spread out just like they do in a balloon when you blow air into it.	2
"I think this evidence could be used because the gas particles are everywhere in the diagram in the notebook and he also said that the balloon grows bigger in all directions, so there is some relation there."	2
Balloons get bigger in all directions when inflated.	0
"Since the teacher is saying the air in a balloon inflates in all directions, it inquires that the gas is spreading out. This helps Charlie because it's seen here that the gas particles are spreading."	1
"When you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions, so should is go around in the box also."	2
"This gives Charlie an example to refer back to, it also gives him a chance to draw a diagram, like Sam"	0
this suppports charlie's claim because the teacher says the ballon grows bigger in all directions and charlie showed the gas particles in spread out in different directions.	1
The gas goes everywhere when poped	0
The balloon grows bigger in all directions sits diverse and spread apart which is what charlie's picture shows.	1
"Charlie's claim has the particles spreading out in all directions, and the evidence says that when gas enters a balloon it causes it to expand in all directions."	1
This can't really support charlie's claim as much but there are gas particles being blown into the balloon as well and the balloon must inflate if the particles were all scattered around taking up more space because it wouldn't really make sense if they were just at the top of the balloon because it wouldn't inflate then.	1
This could be used as yet another real world example of thing we do everyday showing that gas does not clump up and rather they float apart.	0
in the picture the gasses are scattered every where so when you blow a balloon the gasses go every where in a balloon	1
so the gas particles in the balloon are all scattered just think charlies box.	2
this could be evidence because when you blow into a balloon air goes all around it and its bascially gas so if you were to leave gas in a box it would float everywhere	1
The particles go everywhere and fil up the space around them.	0
"Yes, because when we blow the air to the balloon the air sperds at the every corner of the balloon"	1
this could be a supporting claim because its saying when u blow a balloon the particles in the balloon will spread out gust like his claim said it would be	2
This evidence could be used to support Charlie because the balloon represents the gas whereas your breath represents the particles. This could provide a visual representation of how the gas particles go in all directions instead of just up.	2
This evidence can support Sam's claim because the balloon example is showing that the air moves freely in a balloon which is what Sam said.	1
This evidence supports Charlie's claim because maybe the particles we are looking at are from a balloon.	0
because in his picture they spread out far and they looked exactly the same as charlie	0
because the particles went in random directions just like the evidence the teacher told him	0
It used to Sam's claim because the gas go inside the balloon it go around.	1
"This evidence states that since a ballon's gas particles push it out and spread it out, then the gas partcles in the box could spread the box out."	2
I think this evidence can support charlie because he put particles scattered everywhere and the hot air ballon when it grows bigger it goes in every direction so it can help.	1
"all molecules bounce back when they hit each other, so if you let them bounce around enough, they would eventualy spread out."	0
the particles spread out to fill up the empty space	0
"The piece of evidence that Charlie got from his teacher, was also right, because the air particles expand, and try to spread out, than just being clumped up all together. (like a solid)"	0
This information could be used to help charlies claim out because it is saying that the gas particles spresd around in an open area.	0
"The balloons are gas and they float all the way to the sky. If kids saw the balloon flying up to the sky, they look up at the sky and knew that balloon is very high and higher in the sky and they get so good at looking at it at the top."	0
The box might be a "balloon" and gas might be the "air"	0
As though the teacher didn't specify what type of gas she was referring too it could also mean Charlie is possibly right.	0
"The helium inside of a balloon is trying to escape the area and go flying around in all directions, also you are stuffing more and more gas particles into an enclosed space."	1
This could help support Charlie's claim because in his picture the particle are moving in all directions just like the particles in the balloon.	2
