review	label
he probably thought that the bubbles will first scatter and then go to the top	0
"This evidence could be used to support his claim because as shown the the balloons, the gas moves in all directions and fills up the balloon, so he assumes that the gas particles should do that, disperse, since it's both gas."	2
"His teacher said when you add air to a balloon it grows in all directions, implying the air moves in all directions."	1
this will support his claim because he drew that the gas bubbles go everywhere and when the teacher say that he might think he is right	0
because the air is far apart	0
because our breath forces the air all around the baloon	1
It supports charlie's claim by how gas particles bounce around a container in every direction and aren't forced in a certain direction.	0
"when you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions, so it may possibly do that aswell for gas particles."	0
The balloon grows in every direction meaning that the air in it is spreading in every direction to make it bigger which is similar to Charlie's claim saying that the gas in a box after one minute spreads apart in every direction.	2
The teacher is telling Charlie that when you blow air into a balloon that the balloon gets bigger which means gas/air bubbles are expanding the balloon creating it to be bigger and the bubbles are around inside the balloon which means charlie could also be right.	1
The gas is filling space in the balloon and the balloon is stretching and it will do this until it pops	1
"Charlie knows that carbon dioxide, what we breathe out is a gas and it moves out in a balloon."	0
because when you blow a ballon it doesnt just turn into a freanch lookin thing it truns into a roundish ball type of thing	0
because the air speards out	0
"When the balloon doesn't have air the particles are clunch up but when you blow air the particles start moving around, and when the balloon"	1
Sam is thinking just the air is being put in there it would spread like the gas would.	0
A balloon spreads so the air spreads. This supports his claim beacuse thats what the picture is also doing.	2
This helps support Charlie's claim because the air goes everywhere inside the ballon.	1
The particles move all in different directions	0
"After a minuet gas particles will begin to rise and spread out everywhere. For example, when you blow up a balloon the balloon starts off small but then as air is blown in it grows bigger in all directions."	1
This will support Charlie's claim because it is true when you blow air into a balloon all the gas particles go all over the place.	1
"""when you blow into a ballon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions"" so Charlie was also correct."	1
the air spreads out so the gas must as well	0
All of the gas particles are taking up the entire space to fill up the box.	0
"Air is taking up all the available space in the balloon. If you used helium which is a much lighter gas, it would do the same effect."	0
"This could support Charlie's claim because in this situation, the air in the balloon could represent the gas particles because the air in the balloon spreads in all different directions just like the gas particles in Charlie's claim."	2
The paticles are growing bigger in all places like a balloon.	1
"Charlies's teacher told him, ""When you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions."" Charlie claimed that after a minute gas spreads evenly."	1
the air particles don't stay in one place so they move all around in different directions because air can't be controlled in where it would go	0
"""When you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions"" is evidence to Charlie's claim because his claim was the the particles would evenly disperse and the teachers balloon and air example works well with his claim of evenly filling up the space."	2
The partcles are everywhare and not just in the bottom	0
"An air balloon could be an example of how the so called torch emits gas and fills the large air balloon. The gas spreads throughout the balloon and soon, it is ready to be used."	1
The particles expand in the balloon making it bigger	1
that the air ex spansso hes right.	0
because when you blow into a balloon the air you put into the balloon makes it expand and evens it out towards different areas	1
If the balloon grows bigger in all directions then it would mean that the gas is taking up the entire balloon.	1
"Since in a balloon, the air spreads in all directions, why wouldn't it be the same in normal air."	2
charlie says the gas will go into different areas	0
This could help Charlie because it shows that the particles move away and around like in his notebook.	0
because he thinks the gas goes everywhere	0
Gas moves every where in balloons because there is nothing in its way so its always moving in other ways totry to push out/ pop.	1
"You blow air, which is also called gas, into a balloon and it causes it to expand."	0
Charlie argues that the gas is hot so they all spread out from each other.	0
The teacher says when blowing air in a balloon the balloon goes in all directions and Charlie thinks that the particles go all over the place. So Charlie's claim is that the particles go all over the place and the teachers statement help prove Charlies claim.	1
"This proves that if there was air blowing, the particles will space out in sam's drawing."	0
"The teacher said that the gas particles will go in all direction when you blow a balloon, which supports Charlie's claim. Charlie said that the gas particles will spread out in the box, which is the same thing that the teacher said."	2
thats wrong be because there soda and the gas has to beon the top	0
This helps support him claim since when you blow the bubble big it spreads and all the gas particles spread apart.	0
The evidence can be used to support charlie because his evidence showed that the particles spread out and the teacher explained about expanding balloons.	1
This could help his claim because this shows his claim in a real-world problem.	0
"When a balloon expanse the gas molecules spread out in every direction, which would explain the molecules that her drew are spread out."	1
The teacher said that the balloon grows bigger and that is what he drew.	0
"This supports Charlie's claim because it's spreading out in 3 directions, like the balloon."	0
The evidence supports Charlie because the balloon expands when you blow it up so therefor the gas moves around.	1
"In Charlie's claim, gas particles move outward and expands in all directions. According to the teacher, "" When you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions."" This could be used to support Charlie's claim."	1
The gas particles are spread apart	0
"This evidence is used in Charlie's claim because when air particles are left there, then they spread out."	0
Because it is true	0
"This could support Charlie's claim because when air is pumped into the balloon, the molecules start moving faster and they spread out making the balloon bigger."	1
This could be used as evidence as Charlie drew just what the teacher told him in that example: gas particles spreading out.	0
A balloon's air spreads out in all directions supporting his claim of the gas particles spreading out in all directions.	1
"In an analogy if the box is the balloon and the and the air blown in are the gas particles than, thinking analogically the the gas particles will spread in all directions."	2
This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim because the drawing shows that the particles spread out in all directions the same way the balloon grew in all directions.	2
"This supports Charlie's claim because the particle in a balloon start at the bottom, and blow into the rest of the balloon, which is Charlie's claim."	0
"This could be used to support Charlie's claim, because the particles inside the balloon are gas particles, and according to the teacher, they spread in all directions. This matches with Charlie's model, as the particles are spread apart in his model as well."	2
Charlie looks like a balloon so he will get encouragement	0
"The teachers claim supports charlie's claim. Charlie stated that the gas particles would spread out in all directions freely. Therefore, when you blow into the balloon, the gas particles spread throughout the space."	1
"This evidence could be used to support Charlies claim because if the gas particles are continually moving and hitting the sides of the balloon, then the balloon will expand, so when you put gas particles in a box, they will also keep moving."	2
This supports charlie's claim because his gas particles spread out around the space.	0
"Since the molecules spread out when you blow up a balloon, this is similar to Charlie's picture since it also represents molecules spread out."	2
"This supports Charlie's claim because in his claim he talked about the particles spreading out and the teacher stated that when you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions."	1
All the airs spread out making the balloon bigger. As the gas particles spread it moves around.	1
The gas particles in a balloon expands the balloon so the gas particles might spread of in the box and expand it a little.	1
"If you imagine the box as a balloon and the particles inside as air, you can see that the air disperses inside the balloons."	2
"If you blow into a box, the gas particles might spread."	0
"This can support Charlie's claim because the air in the balloon begins to spread, the more added in. As his teacher said, the gas spreads in each direction."	1
"Charlie claims that after a minute, all the gas particles will be spread evenly in the box. When you blow air into a balloon, it grows bigger in all directions, as a result of the air. Since the gas particles are spread in all directions in his drawing, that directly relates to the balloon."	2
The particles are spread out because when you blow a balloon the object expands and the particles have more room to spread out.	1
"This evidence can be used for Charlie's claim by in balloons, the gas particles inside expand and the air becomes more spread out."	1
Charlie could argue that the gas particles are inside of a balloon.	0
"Charlie's claim is supported by this because when you blow into a balloon, it grows bigger in all directions, and this may also be true for gas particles."	2
This evidence supports Charlie's claim because the gas bubbles are spreading out like the gas in the balloon.	2
Charlies' claim can be supported by this evidence because the gas must move around in order to fill up the balloon.	1
"If gas fill the space of a balloon, then it would fill space of the container too."	2
The air expands everywhere and air is made of gas particles so gas particles will also expand.	2
This evidence supports Charlie's claim about the particles being spread out and all around the space.	0
Charlie's evidence would be that gas particles spread out when air is let into a box/balloon.	1
the spread out more.	0
the gas particles spread out and expand the balloon.	1
When you blow in to a balloon the air will scatrer to take up space.	1
charlies bubles have all rised a little and have gone in diffrent directions like the gas in the ballons	1
This means that the particles moved around from an outside force acting upon them. The temperature of the breath could also have effected the movement.	0
This evidence supports it because it states that the gas spreads.	0
This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim since the evidence back ups his claim which is the gas particles go in all directions and are spread out just like the balloon.	2
Water isn't wet because it is a liquid that wets things. Once you come into contact with water you become wet. Until then water is liquid and you are dry.	0
"When you blow air into the balloon, it grows bigger because the gas expands to fill its container. Since this is what Charlie's drawing shows, he can use ti to support his claim."	2
This evidence can claim Charlie's answer as the air is covering the ballon.	0
The gas spreads to fill the balloon.	1
"When you blow air into a balloon, the air goes into all directions so the gas particles will go in all direction too."	2
That when you blow in a balloon all the gas skaters every where.	1
"This evidence could used to support Charlies's claim, because, the teacher said that, ‰ÛÏWhen you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions.‰Û And Charlie drew the gas particles everywhere in the box, saying the spread out."	2
As you blow a balloon the air going into the balloon doesn't inflate in only one direction. The gas causes the balloon to inflate in all directions. Charlie's claim proves this.	1
It shows that charlie is also correct.	0
when you blow up a balloon the gas particles expand the balloon and blow it up which could mean that gas particles in a box could do the same thing	2
Then the gas might be able to stretch out and fill the empty spaces.	0
that since they started at the bottom they then start to go everywhere	0
Charlie says that the particles float around in different directions just like the teacher said happens in a balloon.	2
i think sam is rigth	0
The evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim because in a bath tub when you blow bubbles they fly everywhere and not stick together.	0
"Charlie can use this evidence to support his claim because when you blow a balloon, you are increasing air through the whole thing."	0
"Gas particles constantly move around in the container that it is in. If the particles were closer to each other, they would end up either being a solid or liquid."	0
this can help charlies because he says that the gas spreads out and so does the teacher when you blow a balloon.	2
This could be used to support Charlie's claim because of the fact that the particles will move in all directions which is exactly what Charlie drew in his notebook.	2
"This could be included in Charlie's claim because when you blow air into the balloon you are filling the balloon with particles, causing them to spread out."	1
That in his drawing the particles spread out.	0
it supports charlies answer because the molecules blow up in different directions so he is saying that they molecules move freely	0
The particles going out like his teacher said what would happen with the balloon	2
The particles are going out like his teacher said with the ballon	2
"In charlies the particles are spreading out, and in the balloon the particles are also spreading out."	2
"Charlie's evidence was that the particles were spread out, and because they were spread out the balloon grew more"	1
"Charlie can use a balloon, as his teacher says when you blow a balloon, it grows bigger, to support his claim."	0
This shows that the particles spread apart.	0
"When you blow air into a balloon, there is heat going into the balloon. That's why the particles move around."	0
"If the air in balloons expands, then so will the gas particles."	2
"This evidence could be used to support Charlie's claim because in his claim he describes how the gas particles are all spread out. The evidence states that ""When you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions."" the evidence supports Charlie's claim."	1
because the gas in a balloon go in every direction	1
"Gas particles in a balloon travel everywhere in the given space, which is what Charlie tried to explain in his notebook."	2
"This evidence, ‰ÛÏWhen you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions,‰Û can be used as proof that air molecules spread out individually."	1
then the teacher	0
I agree with charlie because when you blow a balloon it gets bigger and bigger as you keep blowing. causing the gas particles to go everywhere.	1
the gas particles go all around the teacher said that's what charlie drew	0
"Since Sam's diagram was spreading apart and the balloon grows bigger in all directions, he can relate to the balloon spreading to argue his argument."	0
"Charlie think that gas will float in all directions, just like when you blow into a balloon."	2
that the sugar will not go in the middle.	0
is true that a bollon do it like thisb so is ok.	0
the balloon grows bigger in all directions so it supports his claim that gas particles separate.	2
this evidence can support Charlie's claim because . x	0
"Charlie's claim was that the gas particles are more spread apart from each other. His teacher said that ""When you blow air into a balloon, the balloon grows bigger in all directions."" This helps Charlie's claim because in his model it shows how the gas particles are spread apart in all directions."	1
"The particles are everywhere in a balloon, so same is for the box"	2
"In my observations, the particles spread out, going in many different directions."	0
"When you blow a balloon, it gets bigger. So when the gas particles spread, they also get bigger."	1
Because its true that when u blow insdie a balloon it gets bigger in all directions	0
In a balloon the air particles go all over the place.	1
it helps becasue its telling him that the particals have spread because the ballon grew bigger.	1
"It helps her understand what she drew, which allows her to make a strong reasoning."	0
"Charlie's claim was that the bubbles will spread out after 1 minute. The teacher said, that when you blow a balloon, the air inside spreads out just like in his drawing."	2
Because this evidence could be used to show that gas spreads out into all directions.	0
I guess I'll try here too. Charlie could say that the air in the soda is all around in the liquid. I highly doubt though Charlie is correct based on what the teacher told the other guy. Sounds to me like this teacher is setting little Charlie up for failure here.	0
"This is all incorrect, at the start of the section, it started with the particles at the bottom, it was said that it was in it and what would happen to the box after."	0
when the balloon grows the particles fill up the space in the balloon.	1
the gas can cause the balloon from all sides to go each way.	1
All of the particles move all all directions.	0
Maybe Charlie is using a balloon and is trying to find out where the gas travels.	0
the balloon will get bigger when he puts air in it.	0
